Subindex build by Linnet http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5 Created time 22.09.08 09:33:43
? ?
Tim Cook: Good morning.
早上好！
We're so glad you could join us.
很高兴你来加入我们
At Apple, we're fortunate to be surrounded by people
在 Apple 我们非常幸运
who strive to innovate together
聚集了一群奋发创新的人
to create products and experiences that enrich people's lives,
携手打造各类产品和服务 来丰富人们的生活
products that are intuitive and easy to use,
这些产品直观易用
that have a unique integration of hardware and software,
以独特方式将软硬件深度整合
and that are incredibly personal.
而且极具个性化
Today, we're here to talk about three products
今天我们要聊日常生活中
that have become essential in our lives:
必备的三款产品
iPhone, AirPods, and Apple Watch.
iPhone AirPods 和 Apple Watch
They're always with you,
它们始终陪伴在你身边
useful whenever and wherever you need them,
随时随地帮到你
and are designed to work seamlessly together.
且默契配合相互协同
On their own, each is industry leading.
单独来看 都是各自品类中的行业翘楚
Together, they provide a magical experience.
配合起来 则会带来神奇的体验
With one tap, AirPods are instantly set up
只要轻轻一点 AirPods 就设置完成了
and ready to work with your iPhone and Apple Watch,
即刻可与 iPhone 和 Apple Watch 配对使用
and automatic switching allows sound to move seamlessly
自动切换功能可使音频
between any of your Apple devices.
在你的各个 Apple 设备之间无缝切换
There's also incredible integration between iPhone and Apple Watch.
还有 iPhone 和 Apple Watch 之间的美妙配合
Together they provide the convenience of having your notifications
二者共同协作为你带来的便利包括
and messages on your wrist and available with just a glance.
你的通知和信息只需抬起手腕 轻松一瞥就能看到
You can seamlessly hand off phone calls between your iPhone and Apple Watch,
在 iPhone 与 Apple Watch 之间无缝切换通话
and you can set your destination on your iPhone
你也可以在 iPhone 上设置目的地
and your Apple Watch will help guide you along the way.
然后让 Apple Watch 一路给你指引方向
Users can even get their health and fitness data from Apple Watch
用户甚至可以通过 Apple Watch 获取健康和健身数据
and see it on the Health app on their iPhone.
并在 iPhone 的健康 app 中查看它们
These are just a few examples of the unique and powerful ways
上面只是几个例子
our hardware and software are designed to work together,
来展现我们独特而强大的软硬件协作方式
enhancing and enriching the experiences you have with these products.
以此增强和丰富产品的使用体验
This type of integration is something only Apple can do.
这样的整合协调 只有 Apple 能实现
And today we're going to make these products and these experiences
而今天 我们会让这些产品和体验
even better.
进一步升华优化
Let's get started by talking about Apple Watch.
让我们先来谈谈 Apple Watch 吧
Apple Watch has become an essential companion.
Apple Watch 一直是大家不可或缺的好帮手
It's always with you, allowing you to do so much right from your wrist.
它总是陪伴在你身边 让你抬起手腕就能做很多事
It keeps you connected to the things you care about most,
帮你时刻关注自己最关心的事
encourages you to stay active, and monitors your health
鼓励你动起来 监测你的健康
and gets help when you need it.
并在需要的时候为你寻求帮助
And I've received thousands of letters from customers
我收到过成千上万封的用户来信
writing about their personal experiences using Apple Watch.
分享他们使用 Apple Watch 的个人体验
I'd like to share just a few of those stories with you now.
我想和你分享其中的一些故事
Hello Apple
你好 Apple
Dear, Mr. Cook...
亲爱的 Cook 先生
Dear, Tim...
亲爱的 Tim
Dear, Mr. Cook...
亲爱的 Cook 先生
Hello, Mr. Cook...
你好 Cook 先生
I'm writing to you from Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
我在威斯康星州的 Milwaukee 给你写信
I'm writing you from Atlanta, Georgia.
我从佐治亚州的 Atlanta 写来
I'm
我是个铁人三项选手 也是视障人士
I am a 27-year-old high school teacher.
我 27 岁 在高中当老师
I'm a senior in high school.
我正读高中
I only had the watch for two or three weeks.
我才戴上表两三个星期
the watch
这块表 让我训练和比赛的方式大大改观
I was viewing a movie with my wife in our family room...
当时我和太太正在屋里看片子
I was having lunch at one of the spiciest restaurants in San Diego...
我正吃着午饭 这家餐厅的辣在 San Diego 名列前茅
It was a typical summer night.
那是一个夏天的夜晚
I looked around the corner,
我发现角落里有只熊
and a bear was staring right at me.
它也在朝我看
I was doing what we call a dump and return
我在干装卸的时候
when I slipped headfirst into the compactor.
不小心向前滑倒 整个人栽进车斗里
I was skating on a frozen river when the ice gave out.
我在冰冻的河面上溜冰 没想到冰化了
The door closed, and everything went dark.
门关了 我眼前一黑
My longtime friend started grasping his chest.
忽然 我的老友猛地抓住胸口
I was fighting to catch my breath.
我拼命地喘气
I used the watch to study my pulse, and it was wildly erratic.
我用手表测了下脉搏 发现跳得很乱
Things escalated quickly from there.
情况还在迅速恶化
I was getting tired, and I could tell hypothermia was setting in.
我越来越疲惫 已经感到有失温的危险
I go to grab my phone, but my pockets were empty.
我把手伸进口袋 然而手机并不在
I didn't have my phone on me.
我的手机没在身上
As I was trying to figure out what to do,
我不知道该怎么办好
I looked down and saw my watch.
我一低头 恰巧看到了手表
I placed my Apple Watch on his wrist,
我把我的 Apple Watch 戴在他手腕上
and I couldn't believe my eyes.
简直难以置信
An atrial fibrillation notification popped up.
房颤提示立马弹了出来
Holy cow.
我的天
Holy moly.
老天爷啊
I looked down at my Apple Watch,
我看了看 Apple Watch
and my heart rate was 187 beats per minute.
发现心率达到每分钟 187 下
I drove him to the hospital
我马上开车把他送进医院治疗
where he was treated for a heart condition he wasn't aware he had.
他完全没意识到自己心脏出了问题
Dear, Apple,
你好 Apple
my dad was flying our small plane to Vermont.
在我爸驾驶小飞机去 Vermont 的半路
I was asleep in the backseat.
我原本在后座呼呼大睡
I woke up when we were crashing into the tops of the trees.
忽然飞机一头扎进一片树林 把我彻底惊醒了
The plane broke into six pieces,
飞机碎成了六块
and we were miles away from civilization in the freezing cold.
但这里离有人迹的地方有好几英里 而且我们快冻僵了
Then, all of a sudden,
忽然电话铃响了
my Apple Watch started ringing.
是我的 Apple Watch
I forgot I was wearing it.
我都忘了还戴着表
I told my grandma that I'd have to call her back,
我跟奶奶说晚点再打回给她
and I immediately called 911.
然后立刻拨打 911
I whispered to my co-teacher,
我小声对同事说
"I need to go to the emergency room right now."
“我得马上进急救室”
We were advised to head directly to the emergency room.
他们要我们马上去急救室
I held down the button and whispered, "Siri, call 911."
我按下按钮 悄悄说 “嘿 Siri 打给 911”
I dialed 911, and that sucker started ringing,
我打了 911 铃声在这小东西上响了起来
and I was smiling like a brand-new baby.
我开心得像个小孩
Rescuers arrived in minutes.
救援人员几分钟就到了
If I hadn't had the Apple Watch, things could have been much worse.
如果没有 Apple Watch 事情恐怕就糟糕了
I'm so grateful.
我太感激了
From now on, I'll never leave the house without it.
现在 我出门一定戴表
It's amazing.
真的太棒了 这么个小小的设备
Help me
居然能在生活的方方面面都帮到我
My doctor said, "It was your watch that saved your life."
医生告诉我 “是你的表救了你〞
Thanks for helping save my friend's life.
它让我朋友获救了 谢谢
Since the heart event was without other symptoms,
心脏问题会来得毫无征兆
clearly, the watch was my only call to action
这块表提醒了我 让我采取行动
and my only link to the fine medical care that saved my life.
也就是它引导我联系医疗救助 挽救了我的生命
With deep gratitude, Erik.
万分感谢 Erik
Thank you, Hannah.
太谢谢了 Hannah
Sinceramente, Marcos.
由衷感谢 Marcos
Bill.
Bill
Taryn.
Taryn
Sincerely, Dr. Korn.
真心感谢 Dr. Korn
All the best, Shaae.
祝好 Shaae
There are so many ways Apple Watch improves peoples' lives.
Apple Watch 从方方面面改善了人们的生活
These are the reasons we do what we do.
这也是我们努力的初衷
And this year we're introducing our best Apple Watch lineup yet,
今年 我们将推出迄今为止最强大的
by far!
Apple Watch 产品线
To tell you more, here's Jeff.
下面请 Jeff 为你介绍
? ?
Jeff Williams: Each year, Apple Watch sets a new standard
每一年 Apple Watch
for what a smartwatch should be.
都为智能手表带来新的突破
And this continuous innovation has made it the number-one-selling smartwatch
正是这样的持续创新 使它连续七年
in the world for seven years running.
蝉联全球智能手表产品销量冠军
And we're so excited about what's next.
我们对新一代产品充满期待
? ?
This is the new Apple Watch Series 8.
这就是全新的 Apple Watch Series 8
It has all of the things you love about Apple Watch plus even more.
它保留了 Apple Watch 所有备受用户喜爱的优点 而且加入了更多功能
Series 8 is beautifully designed
Series 8 设计精美
and packed with the most advanced sensors and technology.
配备了最先进的各类传感器及技术
It features a big, brilliant, Always-On display with narrow borders
出色的大尺寸全天候显示屏 采用窄边框设计
that push the screen right to the edge.
将屏幕延伸到了边缘
Detailed watch faces like the new Lunar, Astronomy,
各款细节满满的表盘 例如全新的月相、天文
Metropolitan, and Modular look stunning.
大都会和模块等 精美生动
And it's so bright that text and complications are easy to read
明亮的屏幕让文字及各类复杂功能清晰可见
even when your wrist is down.
即使在手腕下垂时
And Series 8 is durable.
而且 Series 8 十分坚固耐用
It's swim proof, dust proof, and crack resistant.
游泳适用 防尘抗裂
To tell you more about Series 8, here's Deidre.
下面请 Deidre 为你详细介绍 Series 8
? ?
Deidre Caldbeck: Series 8 is designed to keep you connected
Series 8 让你
to the people and things that you care about most.
与最关心的人与事保持联系
It motivates you to stay active and fit.
它会激励你动起来 保持健康
With Workouts and Fitness+ there are so many ways to exercise using Apple Watch.
有了体能训练 app 及 Fitness+ 服务 你有无数种方式用 Apple Watch 来配合运动
Series 8 helps keep you safe with fall detection,
Series 8 支持摔倒检测
emergency SOS, and Medical ID.
紧急联络及医疗急救卡 为你的安全保驾护航
It has sleep tracking, Cycle Tracking, and Mindfulness
还有睡眠跟踪 经期跟踪及正念等功能
to give you insights into your body and help you maintain healthy habits.
让你更深入了解自己的身体 并帮助你保持健康的习惯
With best-in-class health sensors that enable ECG,
配备了由各类技术尖端的健康传感器 带来的移动心电图房颤提示软件
irregular rhythm notifications, and blood oxygen,
心律不齐提示及血氧测量功能
it is the ultimate device for a healthy life.
它是健康生活的理想设备
And now, Series 8 brings even more features
现在 Series 8 带来了更多
for health, safety, and connectivity,
健康、安全和连接方面的新功能
starting with an innovative new temperature sensor
首先是一款创新性的全新温度传感器
that takes our commitment to women's health even further.
进一步实现我们对推进女性健康的承诺
And here's Sumbul to tell you about it.
下面请 Sumbul 为你介绍
? ?
Dr. Sumbul Ahmad Desai: Women's health impacts more than just women.
女性健康不仅事关女性自己
It also impacts their families and communities.
也关系到她们的家庭与社区
And menstrual cycles are key to a woman's health,
月经周期对女性健康至关重要
so much so that many physicians regard them as a vital sign.
很多医生将其视为一项生命体征
We added Cycle Tracking three years ago,
我们三年前就增加了经期跟踪 app
and it has helped tens of millions gain deeper insights
它帮助成百上千万人
into their cycles and overall health.
增进了对自己的经期及健康情况的了解
This year, we're introducing a suite of advanced Cycle Tracking features,
今年 我们将增加一系列先进的经期跟踪功能
including valuable information about a critical aspect of women's health:
包括对女性健康至关重要的方面：
ovulation.
排卵期
As always, we build our health features with two fundamental principles.
与往常一样 我们在设计健康功能时 遵循着两个最根本的原则
First, they're developed using scientifically validated insights,
首先 它们的开发以经科学验证的洞见为基础
and second, privacy is at the core,
第二 隐私永远是重中之重
designed to keep your data secure and private.
所有设计都保证数据安全和私密
Utilizing the new temperature sensor in Apple Watch Series 8,
利用 Apple Watch Series 8 的全新温度传感器
you can now receive a retrospective estimate of when you ovulated.
帮你回推估算排卵日
Series 8 has a unique two-sensor design.
Series 8 拥有独特的双传感器设计
There's one temperature sensor on the back crystal, near your skin,
一个温度传感器位于水晶玻璃表背内 接近皮肤
and another just under the display.
另一个则在显示屏下方
This design improves accuracy by reducing bias
这样的设计能提升测量准确度
from the outside environment.
减少外部环境造成的偏差
Nighttime wrist temperature can be a good indicator
夜间手腕温度可以作为
of overall body temperature
全身体温一个很好的指标
because while you sleep, your blood vessels dilate,
因为在睡觉时 你的血管会扩张
increasing blood flow to your limbs.
增加流向四肢的血液
Overnight, Series 8 samples your wrist temperature every 5 seconds
Series 8 会连续整晚以每 5 秒一次的频率
and it can detect changes as small as 0.1° Celsius.
测量你的体温 精确度可以达到 0.1 摄氏度
In the Health app,
在健康 app 中
you'll be able to see nightly shifts from your baseline temperature,
你可以查看你的夜间体温与基线体温的变化对比
which can be caused by things like exercise, jet lag,
引发变化的原因可能包括锻炼、倒时差
alcohol, or illness.
饮酒或是疾病
But tracking temperature changes is even more useful for those who ovulate,
然而跟踪体温变化对于排卵的人帮助更大
because cyclical patterns can reveal the biphasic shift.
因为周期性模式可以揭示双相型体温
The biphasic shift is an increase in body temperature that occurs in response
双相型体温是指因激素变化
to changing hormones, and it can indicate ovulation.
而导致的体温升高 可能意味着排卵的发生
If you're trying to conceive, knowing if and when you ovulated
如果你在尝试怀孕 了解是否排卵以及排卵时间
can inform your family planning
能帮助你做生育计划
and conversations with your health care provider.
并更好地与医护工作者沟通
Today, the most common way to track the biphasic shift
如今 跟踪双相型体温最普遍的方式
is manually with a thermometer and a journal.
是手动使用 体温计和日记本
Series 8 makes this much easier and more convenient
Series 8 将这些努力变得更轻松 更方便
by providing new, automatic retrospective ovulation estimates.
带来了全新的自动回推排卵日估算
Further advancing Cycle Tracking,
经期跟踪功能也有提升
all users on iOS 16 and watchOS 9 can be now notified
现在所有使用了 iOS 16 和 watchOS 9 的用户如果根据经期数据记录
of possible cycle deviations based on logged cycle data.
系统计算出可能存在经期偏差 都会收到提示
You may not realize that common cycle deviations, like persistent spotting
你可能都没有意识到常见的经期偏差 如持续的点滴出血
or prolonged periods, can be symptoms of serious health conditions
或经期延长 可能是严重健康状况的症状
like fibroids, thyroid disorders, or PCOS.
如肌瘤、甲状腺疾病或多囊卵巢综合征
That's why it's so important to know when they occur.
所以 知道它们何时发生至关重要
The temperature sensing capability on Series 8, plus heart rate,
Series 8 的温度传感器功能
and logged cycle data come together to give you a detailed view of your cycle,
加上心率和经期数据记录 让你详细了解你的经期
all of which can be easily shared with your healthcare provider
所有这些都便于你与医护人员分享
to facilitate more informed conversations.
为你们的沟通提供有帮助的信息
We believe privacy is a fundamental human right
我们认为隐私是基本人权
and that your health data is yours and yours alone.
你的健康数据只属于你本人
Your Cycle Tracking data is encrypted on your device
你的经期跟踪数据在你的设备上加密储存
and only accessible with your passcode, Touch ID, or Face ID.
只有用密码、触控 ID 或面容 ID 才能解锁
When using iOS and watchOS with the default two-factor authentication
当 iOS 和 watchOS 开启默认的双重认证
and a passcode,
并使用密码时
Health app data synced to iCloud is encrypted end-to-end,
健康 app 中同步到 iCloud 的数据采用端到端加密
meaning that Apple does not have the key to decrypt the data
也就是说 Apple 没有解密数据需要的密钥
and therefore cannot read it.
因此也无法读到这些数据
Only with your explicit permission can your health data be shared.
只有经过你的明确许可 你的健康数据才会被共享
And you have granular control over the types of data you share
而且你可以精确地控制分享哪种数据
and who you share it with.
与谁共享
Women's health is critically important,
女性健康至关重要
and we're proud to bring these new advanced cycle tracking capabilities
我们很骄傲能为 Apple Watch Series 8
to Apple Watch Series 8.
带来这些先进的经期跟踪新功能
Now back to Deidre.
下面 交给 Deidre
Deidre: Safety features on Apple Watch,
Apple Watch 上的安全功能
like fall detection and emergency SOS, have helped save lives.
比如摔倒检测和 SOS 紧急联络 曾解救很多人于危难之中
There's another emergency situation you never want to find yourself in,
但还有另一种没有人愿意经历的紧急情况
and that's a car crash.
那就是车祸
According to the US Department of Transportation,
根据美国交通部的数据
almost half of the worst crashes occur in rural areas,
将近一半最严重的交通事故发生在偏远地区
and the majority involve only a single vehicle.
而且绝大多数情况下 涉事车辆只有一辆
So we built an innovative new feature to help in situations like this.
我们因此开发了突破性的新功能 用于应对此类状况
Introducing Crash Detection.
这就是 车祸检测
Apple Watch Series 8 can detect if you were in a severe car crash.
Apple Watch Series 8 可以检测到是否发生了严重的车祸
When a crash is detected, it will automatically connect you
检测到车祸发生后 它会自动帮你
拨打急救电话
with emergency services,
provide your location, and notify your emergency contacts.
向接线员提供你的位置 并告知你的紧急联系人
And to tell you more, here's Ron.
下面请 Ron 详细讲解
? ?
Ron Huang: In order to detect the unique forces of a car crash,
为了检测车祸所包含的独特力学
we developed two new motion sensors for Series 8:
我们为 Series 8 设计了两款全新运动传感器
an improved 3-axis gyroscope
包括一个改进版的三轴陀螺仪
and a high-g-force accelerometer.
和一个高 g 值加速感应器
The new accelerometer is capable of measuring up to 256 g's,
新的加速感应器能测量最高可达 256 g-force
allowing it to detect the extreme impacts of a crash.
使其能够检测车祸发生时极端碰撞的情况
And it samples motion four times faster– at over 3,000 times a second–
而且它的运动采样速度快达 4 倍 也就是每秒超过 3000 次
so it can sense the precise moment of impact.
因而能够精准检测到碰撞发生的瞬间
With these new technologies,
依靠这些新技术
we built an advanced sensor fusion algorithm
我们开发了先进的传感器融合算法
to deliver accurate Crash Detection.
实现精准的车祸检测
We started by spending years studying vehicle impacts
我们花了数年时间
at state-of-the-art crash test labs.
在最先进的碰撞测试实验室研究车辆的碰撞
We focused on four main types of severe crashes:
我们关注了四种严重车祸的主要类型
front impact, side impact,
包括正面碰撞、侧面碰撞
rear-end collision, and rollovers.
追尾碰撞和翻车
In each crash test, we captured data from the new gyroscope
在每次碰撞试验中 我们的捕获数据来自新的陀螺仪
and accelerometer as well as from other sensors in Series 8
和加速感应器 以及 Series 8 配备的其他传感器
including the barometer, microphone, and GPS.
如气压计 麦克风和 GPS 等
And then we used machine learning to incorporate all of these signals
然后我们用机器学习 将所有这些信号
into the algorithm,
整合进算法中
which was trained on over 1 million hours
并已经用超过 100 万小时的 现实世界驾驶及碰撞数据
of real-world driving and crash data.
对它做了训练
Series 8 can detect crashes in the most popular types of vehicles
Series 8 可检测到
like passenger cars, SUVs, and pickup trucks.
轿车、SUV 和皮卡车等常见车型 发生的车祸碰撞
Crash Detection runs only when you're driving
车祸检测只有在行车时才会运行
and processes data only around the time of a possible crash,
仅处理大约撞车时间点前后的数据
entirely on your device.
而且完全在设备端进行
That's Crash Detection on Apple Watch Series 8.
这就是 Apple Watch Series 8 的车祸检测功能
We truly hope you never need it,
我们由衷地希望你永远用不上这个功能
but that you will feel a little bit safer every time you get in the car.
不过在车上能多一份安全感
Now, back to Deidre.
下面 交给 Deidre
Deidre: Even with the new temperature and motion sensors working in the background,
尽管有新的温度和运动传感器在后台运行
Apple Watch Series 8 still has all-day, 18-hour battery life.
Apple Watch Series 8 依然能维持 从早到晚 18 小时的续航
But sometimes, like if you're on a long flight
但有时候 你需要坐长途飞机
or without a charger for the night,
或者在外过夜时没有充电器
you need to preserve battery life.
需要延长续航时间
To help with that, we're introducing Low Power Mode,
所以 我们现在使其可以在低功耗下运行
which can give you up to 36 hours of battery life on a full charge.
让充满电后续航最长可达 36 小时
Low Power Mode maintains many of the core features of Apple Watch–
当在低功耗下运行时 Apple Watch 的大部分核心功能保持开启
like activity tracking and fall detection–
比如活动追踪及摔倒检测
while temporarily disabling other features,
并暂时关闭其他一些功能
like Always-On display and auto workout detection,
比如全天候显示屏和自动体能训练检测
providing maximum battery savings with the least impact to the user experience.
在尽量避免影响用户体验的同时 尽可能节约电量
Low Power Mode is available on Series 4 and later running watchOS 9.
运行 watchOS 9 的 Series 4 及后续产品均可在低功耗下来运行设备
Cellular models of Series 8 will also support international roaming.
Series 8 蜂窝网络机型也将支持国际漫游
Apple Watch will now be able to stay connected to your cellular network
Apple Watch 现在可以在你出国时
while you're traveling abroad.
保持相应的蜂窝网络连接
Simply add your Apple Watch to your iPhone roaming plan at little or no cost.
只需要将你的 Apple Watch 加入你的 iPhone 漫游套餐 无需过多花费 甚至可以免费实现
By the end of the year, international roaming will be available
到今年底 全球将有超过 30 家运营商
on more than 30 carriers worldwide.
支持国际漫游
It will be supported on all cellular models of Apple Watch
运行 watchOS 9 的所有 支持蜂窝网络的 Series 5
from Series 5 onward running watchOS 9.
及后续产品都可使用此功能
Apple Watch Series 8 will be available in four colors of 100% recycled aluminum:
Apple Watch Series 8 使用 100% 再生铝金属的 有四种颜色选择：
Midnight, Starlight,
午夜色、星光色
Silver, and Product(RED),
银色和红色
and in three stainless steel finishes: Silver, Gold, and Graphite.
还配有三种不锈钢外观：银色、金色和石墨色
There are also great new colors across our most popular band styles.
我们广受大家喜欢的各个表带类型 也都会加入新配色
We also have exciting updates to both Nike bands,
两款 Nike 表带也有令人兴奋的新设计
including fresh colors for the Nike Sport Band
Nike 运动表带会有新配色
and a new Nike Sport Loop "Just Do It" woven
新款 Nike 回环式运动表带 则将 Just Do It 标识
right into the textile.
融入编织纹理中
And with watchOS 9,
运行 watchOS 9 后
you can use all Nike watch faces
任何 Apple Watch 上
with any Apple Watch.
都能使用所有 Nike 表盘
There are also two stylish new bands for Apple Watch Hermès.
Apple Watch Hermès 也将迎来两款时尚新表带
"H Diagonal" uses hundreds of micro-perforations
H Diagonal 用数百个微孔
to create a sporty pattern of the iconic Hermès H.
打造出充满动感的标志性爱马仕 H
And "Gourmette Metal" features a polished silver chain
Gourmette Metal 则是一条抛光银链
wrapping twice around the wrist for a bold look.
在手腕上缠绕两圈 时尚又大胆
There's also a new "Hermès Lucky Horse" watch face
还有全新的 Hermès 幸运马表盘
that celebrates their equestrian roots.
纪念品牌的马术根源
That's the incredible new Apple Watch Series 8
这就是卓越的全新 Apple Watch Series 8
with temperature sensing, retrospective ovulation estimates,
配有体温感应、回推估算排卵日
Crash Detection, and international roaming,
车祸检测及国际漫游
on top of best-in-class health features
再加上原有的尖端健康功能
like Blood Oxygen, ECG, and sleep tracking.
比如血氧检测 移动心电图房颤提示软件和睡眠跟踪
It has the latest design that users love with an edge-to-edge display,
它拥有备受喜爱的最新全面屏设计
great durability, and fast charging,
极佳的耐用性 支持快速充电
and all the new features of watchOS 9.
还有 watchOS 9 所包含的各种新功能
Apple Watch Series 8 will start at $399 for GPS
Apple Watch Series 8 的 GPS 款 $399 起
and $499 for cellular.
蜂窝网络款 $499 起
And with the purchase of any new Apple Watch,
新购任意一款 Apple Watch
you'll also get 3 months of Fitness+ free.
还会赠送 3 个月的 Fitness+！
You can order today, and it will be available September 16th.
今天开始接受订购  9 月 16 日发售
And that's Apple Watch Series 8.
这就是 Apple Watch Series 8
Now back to Jeff.
下面交给 Jeff
Jeff: I am so incredibly excited about Series 8.
我真的很期待 Series 8
Let's take one more look at this amazing watch.
让我们再看一看这款出色的手表吧
So you've taken up running.
你准备开跑了
Apple Watch has taken up a few new things as well.
Apple Watch 也配备了一些新功能
First, it tracked your distance. Now, it's tracking your stride length.
它先是能跟踪你跑的距离 现在 也能跟踪你的步幅
It learns your favorite route, then lets you race against yourself.
它会熟悉你最喜欢的路线 让你与自己比拼
You're behind.
落后于目标
Yeah, you're behind.
你落后于目标了
When you're swimming,
游泳的时候
it can tell a breaststroke
它能分辨你是在蛙泳
from a backstroke
还是仰泳
from a kickboard.
还是在用浮板
And when you're done,
结束之后
it dries itself off.
它会自动排水
This isn't a dream. Your watch can take an ECG.
这不是在做梦 你的手表有移动心电图房颤提示软件
But if it was a dream,
就算你真的在做梦
that watch would track your REM sleep down to the minute.
这块手表也会追踪你的快速动眼睡眠时间 精确到分钟
It checks your heart rate.
它会查看你的心率
It checks for temperature changes to estimate when you've ovulated.
查看体温变化 回推估算排卵日
It checks out when you're buying spaghetti.
买意面时 它会帮你付款
It could already detect if you fell.
它已经能检测到你是否摔倒
Now the microphone detects impact noise,
现在 麦克风能检测冲撞时的声音
the accelerometer senses rapid deceleration,
加速感应器会检测到迅速的减速
and the barometer measures a shift in pressure
气压计则能测量压力的变化
consistent with an air bag going off.
与气囊弹出时一致
So it can check if you need help after a car crash.
这样 它就能在车祸发生后 查看你是否需要帮助
And hey, it also shows your ground contact time.
嘿 它甚至能显示你的触地时间
Amazing.
真厉害
Have a nice run.
跑步愉快！
Jeff: Next, let's talk about Apple Watch SE.
下面 我们来聊聊 Apple Watch SE
SE has been a huge hit,
SE 非常受欢迎
and for more than 80% of SE customers
超过 80% 的 SE 用户
it's their very first Apple Watch.
是第一次拥有 Apple Watch
They love how SE delivers the core Apple Watch experience
他们热爱配备了 Apple Watch 核心功能
at a more affordable price.
但价格更亲民的 SE
SE is a fantastic way to get started with Apple Watch.
SE 是 Apple Watch 的极佳入门之选
And this year, it gets even better.
今年 它更上一层楼
The new SE will be available in Silver, Midnight, and Starlight–
全新 SE 有三种颜色选择 银色、午夜色和星光色
all in 100% recycled aluminum.
全部使用 100% 再生铝金属
And we've completely redesigned the back case.
我们也彻底重新设计了表背
It's now made of nylon composite materials
现在使用了全新尼龙复合材料
that match perfectly with the three case finishes.
完美适配三种表壳外观
And there's a new production process that reduces its carbon footprint
还使用了新的生产工艺 将碳足迹
by over 80%.
减少 80% 以上
Now, back to Deidre to tell you more.
下面请 Deidre 为你详细介绍
Deidre: The second generation SE continues to deliver the core benefits
第二代 SE 继续保留了
of Apple Watch that users love,
用户喜爱的 Apple Watch 的核心优势
like workout and activity tracking.
比如运动和活动跟踪
It's swim-proof.
游泳适用
It has high and low heart rate notifications,
具有高心率和低心率通知
emergency SOS,
SOS 紧急联络
and fall detection.
摔倒检测等功能
SE also includes the same motion sensors as Series 8
SE 也配备了与 Series 8 相同的运动传感器
to support Crash Detection.
也支持车祸检测
And with AirPods, you can listen to your music anywhere.
搭配 AirPods 让你可以在随时随地畅享音乐
The SE display is 30% larger than that of Series 3.
SE 的显示屏比 Series 3 大了 30%
And SE features the same S8 System in Package that's in Series 8,
SE 还配备了与 Series 8 相同的 S8 SiP 芯片
making it up to 20% faster than before.
速度提升最高可达 20%
SE continues to be the perfect Apple Watch for Family Setup.
SE 依然是 最适合用于家人共享设置的 Apple Watch
With Family Setup, you can use your iPhone to pair watches for your children
有了家人共享设置 你可以用自己的 iPhone
who don't yet have their own iPhones.
为还没有属于自己的 iPhone 的孩子设置手表
Kids can make phone calls and send messages to contacts that you specify,
孩子可以与你设定的联系人打电话以及发送信息
connect to emergency services, and share their location.
也可以联系急救服务 并共享他们的位置信息
And with new features coming soon like the Home app and home keys in Wallet,
配合其他即将推出的新功能 比如家庭 app 和钱包 app 中的家庭钥匙等
Family Setup allows even more independence for kids
家人共享设置让孩子更独立
and more peace of mind for parents.
让家长更安心
SE offers everyone the core features of Apple Watch,
SE 提供 Apple Watch 的核心功能
and now includes the faster S8 SiP,
包括更快的 S8 SiP 芯片
Crash Detection, new case colors with matching back cases,
车祸检测、新表壳配色与匹配的表背
and all the new capabilities of watchOS 9,
还有 watchOS 9 所包含的一切新功能
all at a more affordable price starting at $249 for GPS
价格则变得更为亲民 GPS 款 $249 起
and $299 for cellular.
蜂窝网络款为 $299 起
You can order it today and it will be available on September 16th.
今天就开始接受订购  9 月 16 日发售
We are so excited about the great new features coming to Series 8
我们非常期待 Series 8 和 Apple Watch SE 的各种新功能
and Apple Watch SE, and can't wait for people to start using them.
迫不及待地让大家能用起来
But we're not done yet.
但我们还没有说完
Here's Jeff to tell you even more.
请 Jeff 为你做更多介绍
? ?
Jeff: We've been working on something completely new.
我们一直在打造一款全新的产品
Over the years, we've spoken to acclaimed explorers,
这些年来 我们与著名的探险家
accomplished adventurers, and elite athletes
卓有成就的冒险家和顶尖运动员相互交流
who are drawn to some of the most extreme environments–
他们曾被一些最极端的环境所吸引
like Ray Zahab, an extreme explorer
比如极限探险家 Ray Zahab
who's crossed some of the harshest environments on foot,
曾徒步穿越了一些最恶劣的环境
including the length of the Sahara Desert,
包括横穿撒哈拉沙漠
and expeditions across Antarctica and the Arctic,
并在南极和北极各处进行探险
and Nadia Aly– an accomplished diver,
以及 Nadia Aly 一位出色的潜水员
expedition leader and renowned underwater photographer,
探险队队长 也是杰出的水下摄影师
and Scott Jurek–one of the most dominant ultra-marathon runners in history
还有 Scott Jurek 史上最杰出的超级马拉松选手之一
and a seven-time winner of the Western States 100-miler.
七届 Western States 100-miler 获奖者
Inspired by their stories,
受到他们故事的启发
we set out to create an Apple Watch
我们打造了一款
designed specifically for exploration, adventure, and endurance,
专为探索、冒险和耐力运动 而设计的 Apple Watch
and it's extraordinary.
它无与伦比
This has been years in the making,
这个项目已经酝酿了多年
and we can't wait to show it to you.
我们迫不及待想和你分享了
? ?
Wanted for hazardous journey...
招募启事 旅程危险
long months of complete darkness...
漆黑数月
Bitter cold,
气候严寒
constant danger,
时刻危险
safe return... doubtful.
能否平安归来？未必
Honor and recognition in case of success.
如若成功 将收获荣誉与认可
? ?
Jeff: This is Apple Watch Ultra,
这就是全新的 Apple Watch Ultra
a completely new design reimagined with extraordinary new capabilities
彻底重构的全新设计 搭配卓越的全新功能
that expand the ways you can use Apple Watch.
大大拓展了 Apple Watch 的使用方式
Every detail has been engineered to create the most rugged
每一个细节都是为了打造有史以来最坚固耐用
and capable Apple Watch ever.
最为强大的 Apple Watch 而制造
It starts with the case,
首先是表壳
made from aerospace grade titanium
由航空级钛金属制成
that strikes the perfect balance of weight,
在重量、耐用性
durability, and corrosion resistance.
和耐腐蚀性之间取得完美的平衡
The titanium case extends up to surround the flat sapphire front crystal,
钛金属表壳向上延伸 包裹住蓝宝石玻璃镜面
protecting it from edge impacts that can occur during extreme activities.
保护它免受极端活动期间 可能发生的边缘撞击的影响
And at the center of the 49mm case is our biggest, brightest display
在 49 毫米表壳中央 配备了 Apple Watch 有史以来
ever in Apple Watch,
最大、最明亮的显示屏
making it easier to read in the harshest sunlight.
在最猛烈的强光下也能轻松看清
We also added a new button– the Action button–
我们还加了一个新的操作按钮
in high-contrast "international orange".
并且做成了高对比度的国际橙色
It's customizable and gives users quick physical control for a range of functions.
这个按钮的功能是可定制的 让用户可以对一系列功能快速进行物理操控
The Digital Crown has a larger diameter
数码表冠的直径更大
and coarser grooves,
凹槽更凸出
and the side button stands proud of the case,
侧边按钮也高于表壳侧面
both designed to be used while wearing gloves.
这两项设计都是为了便于在佩戴手套时使用
And the audio system excels when you're out in the elements.
身处大自然中的时候 音频系统表现杰出
We added a second speaker for increased volume.
我们还增加了第二个扬声器 以提升音量
Three strategically placed microphones and advanced software
三个精心布置的麦克风 加上先进的软件
help ensure voice clarity on calls, even in windy conditions.
确保通话音质清晰可闻 风大也不怕
And for maximum connectivity and communication,
为了确保最好的连接性 便于通信
cellular is built into every Apple Watch Ultra.
所有 Apple Watch Ultra 都配备了蜂窝网络
Ultra has the biggest battery of any Apple Watch yet.
Ultra 是所有 Apple Watch 中续航时间最长的
It gets up to 36 hours of battery life on a single charge.
一次充电 最长可达 36 小时的续航！
And Apple Watch Ultra can even
Apple Watch Ultra 甚至
get up to 60 hours of battery life
最长可达 60 小时续航
for a multi-day adventure
来维持数天探险活动所需
using a new battery optimization setting
电池优化设置更新后
coming later this fall.
在今秋晚些时候
And to complement the rugged utility of the hardware,
为了配合坚固实用的硬件
we created our most technical face yet:
我们开发了科技性最强的表盘
Wayfinder.
寻路者
With a host of critical information, it includes a compass in the dial
这款表盘囊括了多种关键信息 包括融入表盘的实时指南针
and can be customized for the mountain, ocean, or trail.
并且可以针对山脉 海洋或野径等环境进行定制
And to optimize for evening conditions, there's Night mode.
为了在夜晚呈现理想的显示效果 还配备了夜间模式
Just rotate the Crown, and the UI turns red
只需转动表冠 用户界面就会变成红色
for better visibility in the dark.
以便在黑暗中更好地看到
Apple Watch Ultra is designed to push boundaries.
Apple Watch Ultra 生来就是要挑战极限
It's a versatile tool for anyone who appreciates outdoor adventure,
这是一款多功能工具 适合各类户外探险
water sports, and endurance training.
涉水运动、耐力运动爱好者
And for each of these, we created a special band
我们还为每类运动都设计了特制表带
as meticulously crafted as the watch itself.
与 Watch 本身一样匠心打造
With explorers in mind, we developed the Alpine Loop.
我们为户外探险者 设计了高山回环式表带
The titanium G-hook securely fastens through the reinforced top loops.
钛金属 G 式表扣 穿过上层表带的套环稳稳固定住
The band is woven using an innovative process
表带采用创新工艺编织而成
that integrates the two layers without any stitching.
无需任何缝合就将上下两层整合在一起
The Ocean Band is molded in a high-performance elastomer
海洋表带是由高性能氟橡胶模制而成
with a tubular geometry, allowing it to stretch for a perfect fit,
利用管状几何形状实现极为稳固的贴合
even over a wetsuit.
即使是佩戴在潜水服外面
The titanium buckle and adjustable loops
钛金属表扣和可调节式回环
secure the band during high-speed water sports.
即使在高速水上运动中也不会脱落
For endurance athletes, we created the Trail Loop.
对于耐力运动员 我们设计了野径回环式表带
The lightweight textile has increased elasticity
质地轻薄 还增加了弹性
for a comfortable, snug fit.
带来舒适的贴合感
It's our thinnest band yet,
这是我们最薄的表带
with a convenient tab for making quick adjustments.
搭配了方便易用的扣件 可进行快速调整
Ultra is a totally new expression of Apple Watch.
Ultra 是 Apple Watch 的全新形态
Whether you're an accomplished athlete or explorer
无论你是一名出色的运动员或探险家
or aspire to try exciting new activities,
或想要尝试激动人心的新活动
we think you're gonna love it.
我们相信你都会爱上这款产品
Here's Julz to tell you more.
下面请 Julz 为你介绍更多内容
? ?
Julz Arney: We set out to make Apple Watch Ultra
我们的目标是让 Apple Watch Ultra
the best sport watch out there,
成为市面上最强大的运动手表
with features for every athlete.
适合所有运动员使用
GPS performance is critical for serious runners and athletes
GPS 性能至关重要 尤其资深跑者和运动员
who want the most accurate metrics.
对指标的准确性要求极高
A typical GPS solution works well most of the time,
一般的 GPS 解决方案 在大多数情况下能很好地完成任务
but some environments are really tricky–
但有些环境确实很棘手
like when tall buildings or dense trees block satellites,
比如当高层建筑或茂密的树木阻挡住卫星时
making accurate GPS readings nearly impossible when training and competing.
在训练和比赛中 就几乎不可能获得精准的 GPS 读数
The famed Chicago Marathon is a great example.
著名的芝加哥马拉松就是很好的例子
It's a notoriously challenging environment for GPS
众所周知 这项赛事对 GPS 性能要求极高
because a big portion is run between skyscrapers.
因为很大一部分是在摩天大楼之间进行的
So we designed a new, precision dual-frequency GPS solution
因此我们设计了一套 全新的精密双频 GPS 解决方案
that, in addition to L1,
除了 L1 频率之外
also includes the latest frequency: L5,
还包括最新的 L5 频率
plus new, custom positioning algorithms.
再加上全新定制的定位算法
In dense urban conditions like this,
在这种高楼林立的城市环境里
Apple Watch Ultra provides the most accurate GPS
Apple Watch Ultra 的 GPS 准确度
of any sport watch in the market.
在市面上所有运动手表中首屈一指
We also brought some great workout updates to watchOS 9
我们还从高水平运动员身上汲取灵感
inspired by high-performance athletes,
为 watchOS 9 的众多体能训练功能 带来了一系列出色的优化更新
with new metrics, views, and experiences
加入了新指标、详细视图
like vertical oscillation, heart rate zones, and custom workouts.
和垂直振荡、心率区间和自定义锻炼等新体验
And now, with the addition of the Action button on Apple Watch Ultra,
现在随着 Apple Watch Ultra 新增的操作按钮
you can make the workout experience more powerful and more precise.
你的体能训练体验可以更强大、更精准
Press the Action button
按下操作按钮
for the most accurate start to your workout.
精确记录体能训练开始时间
For triathletes and duathletes, the Action button lets you instantly transition
铁人三项和水陆两项运动员 可以利用操作按钮
from one leg of your race to the next.
在比赛中瞬间切换到下一项
And later this year, we're enabling a new feature
今年晚些时候 我们还会启用一项新功能
which automatically detects when you arrive at a running track,
当自动检测到你在进行跑道训练时
ensuring the most accurate pace and distance.
确保最准确的配速和距离
The Action button lets you conveniently mark a segment
操作按钮便于你
with a single press for the ultimate track-running experience.
单按一下进行单圈纪录 带来极致的跑道训练体验
For endurance athletes, the bigger battery makes a big difference.
对耐力运动员来说 持久续航的重要性不言而喻
Of course, you can easily complete a marathon with battery life to spare.
当然 就算你跑完一场马拉松 电量也不会耗尽
Using the new low-power workout setting,
通过新的功能设置 可以在低功耗下来使用设备
most athletes can do a 2.4-mile swim, plus a 112-mile bike ride,
可陪伴大部分运动员游泳 2.4 英里 加上自行车骑行 112 英里
and then run a marathon
然后再跑一个马拉松
to complete a long-distance triathlon with full precision GPS and heart rate.
来完成长距离铁人三项 全程保持全精度 GPS 和心率测量
But Ultra is so much more.
但 Ultra 还远不止于此
It's designed to help you explore the most extreme and remote locations,
它旨在帮你探索最极端、最偏远的地点
from freezing-cold mountains at minutes 20° Celsius
从零下 20 度严寒的高山
to the blazing desert heat at 55° Celsius,
到 55 摄氏度或约
or 130° Fahrenheit.
130 华氏度的酷热沙漠
When navigating in the backcountry, a compass is an essential tool.
在偏远地区探索时 指南针是辨别方向的必备工具
So we completely redesigned the Compass app
因此 我们彻底重新设计了指南针 app
with new precision views and added capabilities.
包含一些全新的精准视图 并增加了各种新功能
The orienteering view includes Compass Waypoints to mark a position–
定向越野视图的新功能包括 用指南针航点来标记位置
like the location of the trailhead or your tent–
如登山口或你的帐篷的位置等
and they can be quickly added using the Action button.
并可通过操作按钮来快速添加
And if you get lost or disoriented,
如果你迷路或迷失方向
Backtrack uses GPS data to create a path of where you've been,
回溯功能会用 GPS 数据创建出你走过的历史路径
so you can easily retrace your steps.
便于你回溯自己的脚步
And it turns on automatically in the background when you go off the grid,
而且它会在你在进入野外时 在后台自动开启
just in case.
以防万一
Getting help when you need it is critical,
在最需要的时候能获得救援是无比重要的
especially in the backcountry.
特别是在人迹罕至的地区
That's why Apple Watch Ultra has a built-in 86 decibel siren
因此 Apple Watch Ultra 内置了 86 分贝的警笛
that you can activate using the Action button.
可以用操作按钮开启
It has a unique sound pattern that alerts others to your location
它配备了独特的声音模式 便于最远可达 600 英尺
up to 600 feet, or 180 meters, away.
或约 180 米之外的人 知道你所处的位置
Finally, Apple Watch Ultra has been designed for water sports.
最后 Apple Watch Ultra 也为涉水运动而生
It can withstand the intense dynamic forces of activities
它能承受风筝冲浪
like kitesurfing and wakeboarding,
和宽板滑水等活动时激烈的动态力
and it can go deep below the waves
也能深入海浪之下
because we engineered it to twice the water resistance, WR100.
因为我们使它的防水性翻倍 达到 WR100
Using its new built-in depth gauge, Ultra automatically launches
利用新的内置深度计 淹没在水下时
a new Depth app when submerged
Ultra 会自动启动全新的深度 app
to show current depth, underwater time, and water temperature.
显示深度、水下时间和水温
We also want Ultra to be a great tool for recreational scuba divers.
我们也希望 Ultra 可以成为休闲水肺潜水的好帮手
So it's been certified to EN 13319,
因此 它通过了 EN 13319 认证
the internationally recognized standard for dive computers and gauges.
即潜水电脑及仪表的国际标准
And we're partnering with Huish Outdoors
我们还与 Huish Outdoors 合作
to create an exclusive app that turns Apple Watch Ultra
开发了一款专属 app 让 Apple Watch Ultra
into a capable dive computer for recreational scuba diving
变身功能强大的潜水电脑
to the depth of 40 meters, or 130 feet.
用于 40 米即约 130 英尺以内的休闲水肺潜水
To tell you more about this incredible app,
为你介绍这款神奇的 app
here's Mike Huish,
下面请 Mike Huish
CEO of Huish Outdoors.
Huish Outdoors 的 CEO
? ?
Mike Huish: Our company is world-renowned
我们公司凭借
for powering every aspect of the underwater experience.
为水下体验的各个方面提供助力而享誉世界
And Oceanic has been a leading innovator in scuba diving for over 50 years,
五十多年来 Oceanic 一直是水肺潜水领域的创新先驱
introducing some of the very first dive computers.
我们开发了最早期的潜水电脑
We're thrilled to announce our new Oceanic+ app for Apple Watch Ultra.
我们高兴地宣布 我们为 Apple Watch Ultra 开发了全新的 Oceanic+ app
This is so exciting for anyone interested in scuba diving
对于任何对水肺潜水感兴趣的人来说 这都是振奋人心的好消息
because now the same watch you wear every day is also your dive computer.
因为你现在每天佩戴的手表 也将成为你的潜水电脑！
We've designed Oceanic+ with all the key features
我们设计的 Oceanic+
for recreational scuba divers and free divers.
包括了休闲潜水员和自由潜水员 所需的所有关键功能
And it works seamlessly with our iPhone app to plan your dives.
而且它能与我们 iPhone 上的 app 协同配合 帮你规划每一次下潜
Our dive planner calculates depth and time,
我们的潜水计划工具能计算潜水深度和时间
and integrates dive conditions like tides,
与潮汐、水温等潜水条件整合
water temperature, and even up-to-date information from the community,
甚至包括来自潜水者社群的最新信息
like visibility and currents.
比如能见度和水流等
The best way to experience this is on a real dive,
体验这一点的最佳方式就是进行一次真正的潜水
so let's get in the water.
让我们一起下水吧
Your dive metrics are all simple and easy to read
你的潜水指标在明亮的大显示屏上
on the large, bright display.
全都一目了然
Our app runs the Bühlmann decompression algorithm,
我们的 app 运行布尔曼减压算法
which constantly calculates and monitors dive parameters.
不断计算和监控潜水参数
So from the moment you start a dive,
从你开始下潜的那一刻起
all critical information is just a glance away.
所有关键信息都一览无余
And unlike most dive computers, which require you to perform
与大多数潜水电脑不同
a complex sequence of button presses to find the information you need,
你无需进行一系列复杂的按钮操作 来寻找你需要的信息
our app uses simple gestures.
我们的 app 使用简单直观的手势操作
Rotate the Digital Crown to access additional screens
旋转数码表冠 就能访问其他界面
or press the Action button to set a compass heading.
或是按下操作按钮 来设置指南针方向
Oceanic+ provides all of the safety warnings that you would expect
Oceanic+ 提供市面上最先进的潜水电脑
from the most advanced dive computers today,
支持的所有安全警告
like decompression limits, excessive ascent rate,
例如减压限制、上升速率过快等
and at the end of your dive, safety stop guidance
还包括在潜水结束时的安全停留指导
all smartly color-coded to help make complex information
全都采用巧妙的颜色编码 帮你轻松理解复杂的信息
easy to understand.
轻松理解
Right after the dive, your data–including your GPS entry and exit location–
潜水一结束 你的数据 包括 GPS 进出位置
automatically syncs to your iPhone and the cloud,
就会自动与你的 iPhone 和云端同步
where you can see a summary of your dive profile.
让你查看你的潜水情况概述
And in your logbook, you can sort and search past dives,
在你的潜水日志中 你还可以对过去的潜水进行分类和搜索
and instantly share your adventures with family and friends,
随时与家人、朋友以及社群
as well as the community.
分享你的冒险经历
We can't wait for you to try it out later this fall.
我们期待你在今年秋天晚些时候亲身体验一番
The Oceanic+ app and Apple Watch Ultra together create a powerful
Oceanic+ app 与 Apple Watch Ultra
and easy-to-use dive computer that will inspire more people
携手打造了一台功能强大 且易于使用的潜水电脑
to discover and explore the underwater world.
它将激励更多的人去发现和探索海底世界
Now back to Jeff.
下面 交给 Jeff
So that's Apple Watch Ultra,
这就是 Apple Watch Ultra
the most rugged and capable Apple Watch ever.
有史以来最坚固最强大的 Apple Watch
With a 49mm titanium case,
配备了 49 毫米钛金属表壳
precision dual-frequency GPS,
精密双频 GPS
a customizable Action button, long battery life,
可定制的操作按钮 持久的续航表现
a built-in depth gauge,
内置的深度计
the biggest and brightest display– up to 2000 nits–
最高可达 2000 尼特的最大、最亮显示屏
and all the other great features of Series 8,
以及 Series 8 的所有其他出色功能
it's designed to help you run your longest race,
它能帮你跑完最长的比赛
explore the back country, and dive the world's oceans.
探索偏远的地区并潜入世界各大海洋
And Apple Watch Ultra, as well as our entire watch lineup,
而且 Apple Watch Ultra 及其他新款 Watch 产品
was designed with the environment in mind–
在设计时 就将环境保护考虑其中
from the use of recycled materials
从使用再生材料
to suppliers' use of clean energy during manufacturing.
到供应商在制造过程中使用清洁能源
We're already carbon neutral for our corporate operations,
我们的企业运营已经实现了碳中和
and these efforts move us even closer toward our goal
而这些努力使我们更进一步
to become carbon neutral for our entire product footprint by 2030.
旨在 2030 年之前 实现所有产品碳中和的目标
All models of Apple Watch Ultra will be $799.
所有 Apple Watch Ultra 表款均为 $799
You can order it today,
今天开始接受订购
and it will be available starting on September 23rd.
9 月 23 日发售
Here's another look at the all-new Apple Watch Ultra.
下面 让我们 再一睹全新 Apple Watch Ultra 的风采
? ?
Every explorer has a packing list–
每个探索者都需要一套装备
the essential tools
一套在奔赴未知时
for heading out into the unknown.
必不可少的工具
We put as many of those tools on your wrist as we could.
为将尽可能多的装备加载到你手腕上
The result...
我们打造了
was the new Apple Watch Ultra.
全新的 Apple Watch Ultra
Ultra's design pushes the boundaries
一身突破极限的设计
so you can do the same.
只为助你全力突破
The rugged, yet lightweight, titanium case extends
坚固而轻盈的钛金属表壳
to protect the flat sapphire crystal
四边裏护平面蓝宝石玻璃表镜
and can endure temperatures that fall below zero
经得起零下的严寒
or climb 130° above it.
也无惧 130 华氏度的酷热
Into the unknown, you'll want the battery to last for days.
踏足无人之地 尤其需要电池能继日不断
That's why Ultra was built with a larger battery
因此 Ultra 配备了更大的电池
for multi-day use on a single charge.
充满一次电 续航时间以天计
You'll also need a map.
你还需要地图
Or better yet, a dual-frequency GPS
最好直接上
with pinpoint accuracy.
定位精准的双频 GPS
The Compass has been redesigned
指南针经过重新设计
and now has waypoint marking and Backtrack,
还有航点和回溯功能
dropping points along your route to keep you found
沿途标记航点 处处有迹可循
when the conditions leave you lost.
避免迷失方向
A turn of the Crown engages Night mode,
旋转数码表冠 开启夜间模式
which removes retina-altering blue light
同时去除影响视网膜的蓝光
to ease the strain on your eyes in the dark.
减轻双眼在黑暗中的压力
Beside the bigger, brighter screen
又大又亮的显示屏旁边
is its most versatile tool–
是操作按钮
a customizable Action button.
既灵活多用 也可自定义
One push lets you track race segments,
一按即可标记训练分段
find a way out,
查找路线
or start up a dive computer,
或启动潜水电脑
which is now strapped to your arm,
没错 就是你手腕上戴的这个电脑
tracking everything from depth to water temperature.
从潜水时间到水温 各种数据都能跟测
The micro-polished sapphire surface and sealed case
精细抛光的蓝宝石玻璃表面和高度密封的表壳
result in an Apple Watch twice as water resistant
实现了高达两倍的防水性能
as any Apple Watch to come before it.
超越以往任何一款 Apple Watch
And the audio system's three microphones triangulate
三麦克风阵列 对音频进行三角测量
so you can be heard
天气再恶劣
even in extreme weather.
也能为你传音
Of course, none of this matters if it falls off your wrist.
当然 戴得稳这一切才有意义
Which is why we've designed three new bands–
三款全新表帯就是为此而生
Alpine, Trail, and Ocean–
高山 野径 海洋
for specific environments
驾驭不同环境
and maximum comfort,
带来超高舒适度
to endure long runs,
能耐受长跑
hard falls, and ripping currents.
能承受跌撞 也能破浪前行
Apple Watch Ultra is an essential tool
无论挑战什么
for essentially anything.
Apple Watch Ultra 都是头号装备
So what will your anything be?
你想挑战点儿什么？
? ?
Jeff: And that's the Apple Watch lineup for the fall,
这就是今秋的 Apple Watch 产品线
with Apple Watch SE providing core features at an even more affordable price,
Apple Watch SE 以更亲民的价格提供所有核心功能
Apple Watch Series 8 with Crash Detection,
Apple Watch Series 8 则配备了车祸检测
and a temperature sensor that enables new women's health features
温度传感器实现了新的女性健康功能
in a design users love.
并以用户喜爱的设计呈现
And finally, Apple Watch Ultra,
最后还有 Apple Watch Ultra
our most rugged, capable Apple Watch yet.
迄今为止最坚固耐用 最强大的 Apple Watch
This is our best lineup ever,
这是我们有史以来最优秀的 Watch 产品线
and we can't wait for users to experience them.
我们迫不及待地期待用户来亲自体验
And now, back to Tim.
下面 交给 Tim
Tim: I'm so excited about Apple Watch Ultra.
我非常期待 Apple Watch Ultra
It's a great addition to our fantastic Apple Watch lineup,
这个新成员加入到 Apple Watch 产品线
which just keeps getting better and better.
使其更加强大
Now, let's turn to AirPods.
下面 让我们来聊聊 AirPods
Just like Apple Watch, AirPods have become essential
和 Apple Watch 一样 AirPods 已经成为
for so many people.
很多人的日常必备产品
Whether listening to music on a run
无论是在跑步时听音乐
or watching your favorite movie,
还是观赏你最爱的电影
AirPods work seamlessly with Apple Watch and iPhone,
AirPods 都能 与 Apple Watch 和 iPhone 无缝协作
and they provide an incredible audio and cinematic experience
它将卓越的无线音频和观影体验
with the simplicity and convenience our users love.
与用户喜爱的简单与便利结合在一起
In fact, AirPods are the best and most popular headphones in the world,
事实上 AirPods 是全球领先且最受欢迎的耳机
and AirPods Pro have become our most popular model,
AirPods Pro 是我们最受欢迎的机型
featuring exceptional Active Noise Cancellation
兼具出色的主动降噪功能
and unrivaled sound quality.
和无与伦比的音质
We're excited to introduce the next generation of AirPods Pro,
很高兴为你介绍新一代 AirPods Pro
our most advanced AirPods yet.
我们迄今为止最先进的 AirPods！
? ?
To tell you more about the new AirPods Pro, here's Mary-Ann.
下面请 Mary-Ann 为你介绍新款 AirPods Pro
? ?
Mary-Ann Rau: At the heart of AirPods Pro is our brand-new H2 chip,
AirPods Pro 的核心是我们全新的 H2 芯片
providing an incredible upgrade to performance from H1
与 H1 相比 实现了大幅性能升级
with high bandwidth connectivity to unlock breakthrough audio experiences
配备高带宽连接 所实现的突破性音频体验
that only Apple silicon can deliver.
只有 Apple 芯片能做到
The exceptional sound quality of AirPods Pro is also now transformed
AirPods Pro 极为出色的音质也进一步优化提升
with a new low distortion audio driver
由一个全新的低失真度驱动单元
and a custom amplifier to power it.
和一个定制的放大器驱动
So whether you are dancing to J Balvin or relaxing to SZA,
不论是伴着 J Balvin 的音乐舞动 还是听着 SZA 的音乐放松心情
you will hear even more detail and clarity
你都能在更广的声音频率范围内
across a wider range of sound frequencies.
听到更多更清晰的细节
These advances come together in a magical way with Spatial Audio,
这些功能提升整合在一起 带来奇妙的空间音频
which takes the listening experience to the next level
将聆听体验带入全新维度
by making sound feel like you are on stage
让你仿佛置身舞台中央
with your favorite band performing around you.
最喜欢的乐队就在你的周围表演
? ?
We are taking this experience even further
而我们将这样的体验进一步提升
with Personalized Spatial Audio.
带来了 个性化空间音频
With iOS 16, you can use the TrueDepth camera on iPhone
配合 iOS 16 你可以使用 iPhone 的原深感摄像头
to create a personal profile for Spatial Audio,
创建空间音频个人轮廓资料
because the way we all perceive sound is unique
因为每个人接收到的声音
based on the size and shape of our head and ears.
因头部和耳朵的大小和形状不同而各有千秋
Personalized Spatial Audio will deliver the most immersive listening experience
个性化空间音频带来了最沉浸式的聆听体验
by precisely placing sounds in space that are tuned just for you.
通过将声音精准地映射到 专为你调校的虚拟空间中
Another feature our users love is Active Noise Cancellation,
另一个深受用户喜爱的功能是主动降噪
which has been a game changer.
这是一个巨大的突破
It reduces unwanted noise,
它可以降低恼人的噪音
so you can better hear your favorite song while on the go.
让你在路上也能更好地聆听喜爱的歌曲
To create a next-generation experience, H2 delivers advanced computational audio
为了创造新一代的体验 H2 解锁了
previously unable to run on a device of this size.
以前无法在这种尺寸的设备上运行的 先进计算音频
This, combined with optimizing the placement of the acoustic vent
再结合优化的声学通气口和麦克风位置
and microphones, now enables up to double the amount of noise cancelled
降噪能力翻倍提升
over the original AirPods Pro,
相比初代 AirPods Pro
delivering even greater focus when you want to be immersed in the moment.
当你想要沉浸在当下时 让你拥有更多专注力
A great in-ear fit also helps to provide passive noise reduction.
出色的入耳式贴合度则实现了被动降噪
With a new, extra small ear tip, even more people can enjoy
新增了 XS 号耳塞
and comfortably wear AirPods Pro throughout the day.
让更多人可以长时间舒适地佩戴 AirPods Pro
? ?
When you want to be connected to the world around you,
而当你想和周围世界接触时
there's Transparency mode.
可以启用通透模式
With the power of H2, we're taking this experience to the next level
借助 H2 的能力 我们进一步优化了这一体验
with Adaptive Transparency,
带来了自适应通透模式
which dynamically reduces the volume of harsh environmental noise
它能动态调整恶劣环境噪音的音量
like heavy construction.
比如巨大的施工噪音
This is made possible because it processes at 48,000 times per second
能做到这一点 是因为它的处理速度达到每秒 48000 次
to react instantaneously to any high-decibel noise you are exposed to.
能立刻对高分贝的噪音做出反应
? ?
Next, let's talk about how you control all of these great experiences.
接下来 让我们聊聊 如何操控所有这些出色的体验
The force sensor on AirPods Pro
AirPods Pro 上的力度感应器
brought the capability to play or pause media
可以随时播放、暂停媒体内容
and answer calls to keep you in the moment.
及接听电话 在你需要的时刻
Today, we're taking that convenience even further by introducing touch control,
现在我们将这样的便捷性进一步提升 为你带来 触控操作
which adds a capacitive sensing layer so you can adjust volume
通过新增的电容感应层
with a light swipe up or down.
让你可以在耳机柄上 轻轻上下滑动来调节音量
The new AirPods Pro with H2 are not only more powerful,
配备了 H2 的全新 AirPods Pro 不仅更加强大
they are far more power efficient,
能效也更高了
delivering even longer battery life.
续航时间更胜以往
Now, you will have up to 6 hours of listening time from a single charge,
一次充电 你就能获得 最长可达 6 小时的聆听时间
which is a 33% increase over the original AirPods Pro.
比初代 AirPods Pro 增加了 33%
And with the charging case, you will have up to 30 hours
搭配充电盒 新款 AirPods Pro 的聆听时间
of total listening time,
最长可达 30 小时
which is an increase of 6 hours.
比上一代增加了 6 个小时
The charging case is also core to the convenience of AirPods Pro.
充电盒也是 AirPods Pro 方便易用的关键
Today, Find My can help you locate AirPods Pro
现在 查找 app 可以帮你寻找丢失的 AirPods Pro
because each headphone can individually play a sound.
因为每一只耳机都能单独播放声音
With the new AirPods Pro,
如果你遗落了新款 AirPods Pro
if you happen to misplace the charging case,
的充电盒
precision finding will help you navigate directly to it
精确查找功能将利用 U1 技术
with U1 technology.
将你直接带到它所在的位置
We have also added a speaker to the bottom of the case
我们还在充电盒底部添加了一个扬声器
to help you find it by playing louder tones.
能播放更响亮的音调 帮助你寻找它
And the speaker will indicate pairing, low battery,
这个扬声器也会在配对、电池电量不足
and when charging has started.
以及充电开始时发出提示音
To make charging easier, in addition to the Lightning cable,
为了让充电变得更容易 除了闪电连接线
you can now use your Apple Watch charger
现在 你还能直接使用你的 Apple Watch 充电器
as well as MagSafe or other Qi-compatible chargers.
MagSafe 或其他 Qi 认证的充电器
And with the addition of a lanyard loop to the side of the case,
我们还在充电盒侧面增加了挂绳孔
your AirPods Pro will always be within reach.
便于你触手可及自己的 AirPods Pro
These are the breakthrough 2nd generation AirPods Pro
这就是创新突破的第二代 AirPods Pro
powered by H2,
由 H2 芯片驱动
making our most popular AirPods even better.
让最受欢迎的 AirPods 更加出众
We've built AirPods Pro with the environment in mind.
在打造 AirPods Pro 时 我们始终牢记保护环境
All magnets are made with 100% recycled rare earth elements,
所用的所有磁铁 都是由 100% 可再生稀土元素制成
and all outer plastic wrap from the packaging is removed.
也移除了所有外包装上的塑料膜
And you can recycle all AirPods models.
所有 AirPods 型号都支持回收
Just bring them to your nearest store or mail them in.
可以将它交到你附近的 Apple Store 或直接寄给我们
The new AirPods Pro are available for $249,
全新 AirPods Pro 为 $249
and you can order on September 9th.
9 月 9 日开始接受订购
They're available on September 23rd with free engraving, including Memoji.
9 月 23 日发售 提供免费镌刻服务 支持拟我表情
We can't wait for you to experience the future of AirPods.
我们很期待你能体验新一代的 AirPods
Now, back to Tim.
下面 交还给 Tim
? ?
Tim: The new AirPods Pro and Apple Watch models are incredible products.
新款 AirPods Pro 和 Apple Watch 都是卓越的产品
They bring more capability wherever you go.
它们时刻伴你同行 为你带来更多功能
And they're designed to work seamlessly with the most essential product of all:
它们在设计上也与最不可或缺的产品默契配合
iPhone.
那就是 iPhone
People love iPhone and it's an important part of our daily lives.
人们喜爱 iPhone 它是我们日常生活必不可少的重要部分
We're constantly challenging ourselves to raise the bar
我们不断挑战自我 提升标准
to make it better and even more loved.
让 iPhone 变得更好 更值得喜爱
So let's take a look at the new iPhone.
让我们一起来看一看全新 iPhone 吧
? ?
As you can see, we're going big with iPhone 14,
如你所见 我们为 iPhone 14 带来了重大更新
and even bigger with iPhone 14 Plus.
还推出了更大的 iPhone 14 Plus
Here's Kaiann to tell you all about it.
下面请 Kaiann 为你介绍
? ?
Kaiann Drance: The popular 6.1" size of iPhone 14
除了备受欢迎的 6.1 英寸 iPhone 14
is joined by the new, larger 6.7" size of iPhone 14 Plus.
我们还推出了全新更大尺寸的 6.7 英寸 iPhone 14 Plus
With a larger display, you can enjoy more content
更大的显示屏意味着 你可以在浏览网页时
when browsing the web.
畅享更多内容
You can see more text or larger text.
你可以看到更多或更大的文本
It looks great with the incredible features of iOS 16,
出色呈现 iOS 16 的各类出色功能
like the new Lock Screen
比如全新的锁屏界面
and iCloud shared Photo Library.
以及 iCloud 共享图库
You can even get more workout details in the Fitness app
你可以查看更多健身细节
with the new Enhanced Workout Summary.
通过健身 app 中更新后的锻炼概要
With a larger display,
更大的显示屏
you have more area to watch your favorite show
也让你有更大的区域 无论是观看最喜欢的节目
or play your most intense game.
或是玩最激烈的游戏
iPhone 14 also has an updated internal design
iPhone 14 也更新了内部设计
that improves thermal performance, which is great for staying in the action longer.
提供更好的散热表现 适合更长时间的运作
Both models have the gorgeous Super Retina XDR display
两款机型均配备绚丽的超视网膜 XDR 显示屏
with OLED technology that supports 1200 nits peak HDR brightness,
采用 OLED 技术 支持 1200 尼特峰值 HDR 亮度
two million-to-one contrast ratio, and Dolby Vision.
2000000 : 1 的对比度以及杜比视界
iPhone 14 is designed to last,
iPhone 14 经久耐用
so you can count on it to be there for you.
随时随地都是你可靠的伙伴
Both models have Ceramic Shield–
两款机型均配备超瓷晶面板
tougher than any smartphone glass–
比任何其他智能手机玻璃都更坚固
aerospace grade aluminum, and water and dust resistance.
航空级铝金属 抗水防尘
They come in five gorgeous colors: Midnight, Starlight,
一共有五种精美外观：午夜色、星空色
a great new shade of blue, a strikingly elegant purple,
靓丽的全新蓝色、优雅惊艳的紫色
and a truly eye-catching PRODUCT(RED).
以及亮眼的红色
Users depend on their iPhone for so many things,
用户们在很多事情上都需要依靠 iPhone
which is why iPhone 14 delivers all-day battery life.
因此 iPhone 14 带来了 满足一天所需的电池续航
iPhone 14 Plus lasts even longer throughout your day
iPhone 14 Plus 的续航 甚至在一天中能维持更久
with the best battery life ever in an iPhone.
是迄今为止续航最长的 iPhone
The larger display and best battery life
更大的显示屏和最出色的电池续航
were previously only available
之前是我们的
in our Pro Max models,
Pro Max 机型独占的
and now we're bringing it to even more people.
现在我们将其带给更多用户
Now, let's talk about performance.
接下来 我们来聊一聊性能
iPhone 13 Pro introduced an amazing chip:
iPhone 13 Pro 推出了惊人的芯片
the A15 Bionic with a 5-core GPU.
配备 5 核图形处理器的 A15 仿生
It's a powerhouse that unlocks extraordinary features
它的强大性能驱动了一众卓越的功能
and delivers great power efficiency, privacy, and security.
并实现了出色的能效、隐私和安全保护
Now we are bringing this proven, Pro-level performance to iPhone 14.
现在我们将这毋庸置疑的 Pro 级性能 带到了 iPhone 14 上
The 5-core GPU is 18% faster,
5 核图形处理器速度提升达 18%
enabling even smoother graphics in computationally heavy workloads
带来更流畅的图形表现 即便是处理复杂游戏
like complex gaming.
等计算繁重的工作负载
It has a powerful 6-core CPU
它拥有强大的 6 核中央处理器
with two high-performance
包括两个高性能核心
and four efficiency cores,
和四个高能效核心
and a 16-core Neural Engine
以及一个 16 核神经网络引擎
that pushes the limits of machine learning.
进一步提升机器学习的极限
Since its introduction, A15 continues to be faster
A15 自从问世以来 让任何价位段的任何竞争对手
than all the competition at any price.
都只能望尘莫及
A15 is essential to iPhone 14.
A15 对于 iPhone 14 来说至关重要
And with a custom image signal processor,
凭借定制的图像信号处理器
A15 also powers innovative features in the amazing new camera system.
A15 实现了全新摄像头系统的众多创新功能
Here's Caron to tell you more.
下面请 Caron 为你介绍
? ?
Caron Thor: iPhone is always with you
iPhone 与你时刻相伴
and ready to quickly and effortlessly capture your life's moments.
让你随时可以快速轻松地捕捉精彩的生活瞬间
Last year, over three trillion photos were taken with iPhone!
仅去年 就有超过 3 万亿张照片 是用 iPhone 拍摄的
We develop unique, state-of-the-art camera technology
我们在研发独特的先进相机技术的同时
while staying true to the craft of photography.
始终忠于摄影艺术本身
Lighting is a fundamental part of getting the best shot possible.
光线条件是能拍出好照片 最根本的一个要素
It plays such an important role in capturing everyday memories
无论是捕捉日常回忆还是惊人时刻
and jaw-dropping moments.
它的作用都非常重要
iPhone enables gorgeous photo capture across the entire range of light–
iPhone 使得 在各种光线条件下拍出精美照片成为可能
from bright light, where colors come alive,
从色彩生动的明亮光线
to low light, like indoors,
到室内等低光环境
to nighttime scenes.
再到夜间场景
And iPhone 14 again sets the standard for photo
iPhone 14 再一次突破了 照片和视频拍摄的标准
and video capture regardless of where you are.
无论你身处怎样的条件中
It has a new 12MP Main camera with a larger sensor,
全新的 1200 万像素主摄 配备了更大的感光元件
and larger pixels at 1.9 microns.
以及 1.9 微米的更大的像素尺寸
It has a larger f/1.5 aperture
更大的 ?/1.5 光圈
and sensor-shift OIS
和传感器位移式光学图像防抖功能
for a powerful Main camera upgrade and takes stunning shots everywhere.
实现了强大的主摄像头升级 便于在各种环境中拍出令人惊叹的照片
The faster aperture allows better motion freezing,
更大的光圈可以更好地定格物体移动的瞬间
showing off vibrant colors that bring the scene to life
展现出鲜艳的色彩  彰显出色的质感和细节
with great texture and detail.
使场景栩栩如生
It delivers a 49% improvement in low light capture,
在低光拍摄方面有了 49% 的提升
for more vibrant color and better results in challenging lighting environments,
在具有挑战性的照明环境中 提供更鲜艳的色彩和更好的效果
while making Night mode exposure twice as fast.
且夜间模式的曝光速度提升快达两倍
And the Ultra Wide camera takes incredible-looking photos and video,
超广角镜头能拍摄令人眼前一亮的照片和视频
which is great for wider shots and unique perspectives.
非常适合拍摄视角更宽且独特的场景
The front camera enables great-looking selfies,
前置摄像头让你能拍出更好看的自拍
high quality video during FaceTime, and so much more.
以及更高画质的 FaceTime 视频通话等
iPhone 14 has a new TrueDepth camera.
iPhone 14 还配备了新的原深感镜头！
It has a faster f/1.9 aperture
它拥有更大的 ?/1.9 光圈
for a 38% improvement in low light capture for photos and video.
照片和视频的低光拍摄提升了 38%
The new front camera has autofocus for the first time,
新的前置摄像头首次加入了自动对焦功能
so it can focus clearly at multiple distances.
可以在多个距离上进行清晰对焦
Together with TrueDepth capabilities,
再加上原深感镜头的功能
the front camera now has a hybrid system
新的前置摄像头现在通过一套混合系统
that can focus faster, even in low light.
实现更快对焦 即使在低光条件下也可以
So you'll get better selfies, group shots can be in focus from farther away,
这样 你就能拍出更好看的自拍 拍合影时可以从更远的地方对焦
and you'll be able to show off great detail up close.
并近距离展示出色的细节
Low light environments can be a unique challenge with photography.
低光环境对摄影来说是一个独特的挑战
We've made incredible progress in capturing in low light over the years
这些年来 我们在低光摄影方面取得了长足进步
with increasingly larger sensors and faster apertures,
更大的感光元件 更大的光圈
more advanced lenses–
更先进的镜头
all paired with intelligent software
再结合智能的软件
and our powerful Apple silicon that result in incredible capabilities for low light.
以及我们强大的 Apple 芯片 来了卓越的低光摄影功能
Deep Fusion is a great example.
深度融合就是一个很好的例子
It's a huge achievement in computational photography
这是计算摄影的一项巨大成就
and uses the powerful Neural Engine
用强大的神经网络引擎
to combine multiple frames into a single image.
将多个帧组合成一个图像
This delivers extraordinary detail
从而呈现出非凡的细节
and preserves even the subtlest textures in these mid- to lower-light environments.
并保留最微妙的纹理 即便是在中到低光拍摄时
Now, we are taking our image pipeline further
现在 我们对图像管线进行进一步优化
by applying Deep Fusion much earlier in the process on uncompressed images.
将深度融合在图像合成过程中前置 应用于未经压缩的图像
This retains much more information and detail,
这么做能保留更多信息和细节
and enables rendering of more colors and brighter colors.
也能渲染更多和更明亮的颜色
This new process unlocks our biggest step forward yet for low light performance.
这个新流程也推动了我们 在低光摄影性能上实现的最大突破
We call it Photonic Engine.
我们称其为 光像引擎
This is our enhanced image pipeline
这是我们优化后的图像管线
that dramatically improves low-light photos.
可显着改善低光照片的质量
It goes beyond what hardware alone can provide.
远超仅凭硬件能实现的效果
The best part is that it benefits every camera.
最棒的是 每个摄像头都能从中获益
When compared to iPhone 13,
与 iPhone 13 相比
it enables photo low light improvement up to two times on the front camera,
低光拍摄的提升改善 在前摄像头上最高可达 2 倍
two times on the Ultra Wide camera,
超广角摄像头最高可达 2 倍
and two-and-a-half times on the new Main camera.
在新的主摄上最高可达 2.5 倍！
You'll get photos with much better detail and color,
你将得到细节与色彩大幅改善的照片
helping you remember the moment the way you lived it.
帮你更生动地回忆起每一个瞬间
There's also a big improvement to video this year.
今年 视频方面也有了很大提升
iPhone leads the industry with the highest quality video
iPhone 以最高质量的视频引领全行业
and has great stabilization.
并具有出色的防抖
It now has a new, even more advanced stabilization mode
现在 我们新增了一个更先进的防抖模式
that gives users a powerful tool when capturing moments on the move.
给用户一个强大的工具用来捕捉各种移动的瞬间
This is Action mode.
这就是 运动模式
It uses the full sensor with more overscan and advanced roll correction
它使用整个感光元件 通过更多的过扫描和高级滚动校正
to make video look incredibly stable when you're in middle of the action.
让你在动态中拍摄的视频看起来特别稳定
Simply toggle it on for great-looking, smooth video,
只需打开运动模式就能拍出丝滑流畅的视频
without having to carry extra gear like a gimbal.
且无需携带像云台这样的额外装备
It also supports and Dolby Vision HDR.
这一模式同样支持杜比视界 HDR
The new iPhone 14 camera system is a huge upgrade,
iPhone 14 全新的摄像头系统带来了重大升级
enabling incredible-looking shots across the entire range of shooting conditions.
在各种拍摄条件下 助你拍出惊艳的照片
Back to you, Kaiann.
交还给你 Kaiann
? ?
Kaiann: Now let's talk about connectivity.
现在 我来聊一聊连接性
iPhone has powerful capabilities
iPhone 拥有一系列强大的功能
that help our users stay in touch on the go.
帮助用户随时随地保持联系
This is especially true for 5G, enabling super fast downloads,
5G 尤其是如此 支持超快速下载
better streaming, and real-time connectivity.
更流畅地看流媒体以及实时连接
And momentum for 5G is stronger than ever,
5G 的发展势头越发强劲
with over 250 carriers around the world on 5G.
现在全球有超过 250 家运营商支持 5G
We've also made big improvements to cellular technologies like eSIM,
我们还对 eSIM 等蜂窝技术进行了重大改进
making it even easier to connect.
使连接变得更容易
An eSIM is a digital SIM that eliminates the need for a physical SIM card.
eSIM 是一种数字 SIM 卡 不再需要使用实体 SIM 卡
With eSIM, you can quickly transfer an existing cellular plan
凭借 eSIM 你可以快速转移现有的蜂窝数据计划
or get a new cellular plan, all digitally.
或是获取新的蜂窝数据计划 全都以数字的方式实现
You can even store multiple eSIMs on the same device,
你甚至可以在同一台设备上存储多个 eSIM
meaning multiple cellular plans and phone numbers.
也就是多个蜂窝数据计划和电话号码
And it's more secure.
安全性还更高
Someone can't remove the physical SIM card
即使你的 iPhone 丢失或被盗
if your iPhone is lost or stolen.
他人都无法将 SIM 卡移除
eSIM setup is easy.
eSIM 设置起来非常简单
In just a few simple steps, users are ready to make calls,
只需几个简单的步骤 用户就可开始拨打电话
send messages, and browse the web.
发送信息和浏览网页
You can even do this without a Wi-Fi connection.
甚至不需要连接 Wi-Fi 就能完成设置！
Extensive planning and testing with carriers
为了实现 iPhone 的 eSIM 体验
helped enable the iPhone eSIM experience.
我们与运营商一起做了大量的规划和测试
This includes the US, where eSIM support has skyrocketed,
在美国 AT&T、T-Mobile、Verizon 等运营商
thanks to AT&T, T-Mobile, Verizon, and many more.
对 eSIM 的支持迅猛增长
Now, for the first time, all US models no longer have the SIM tray,
从现在开始 首次实现了 所有美国版 iPhone 都不再有 SIM 卡槽
so you don't have to deal with a physical SIM card anymore.
你不必再需要实体 SIM 卡
eSIM provides a simpler way to activate and use iPhone.
eSIM 带来了更简单的方式 来激活和使用 iPhone
Next, let's talk about some features
下面我们来聊一些
that make iPhone even more essential.
让 iPhone 变得更加不可或缺的功能
iPhone is there when you need it most.
在你最需要的时候 iPhone 就在你身边
That confidence is especially important in moments where your safety is at risk.
在你的安全受到威胁时 这份信心尤为重要
With iPhone 14, we have two critical new safety features.
iPhone 14 新增了两个关键的安全功能
It has Crash Detection–
iPhone 14 支持车祸检测
the same feature you just heard about on new Apple Watch models.
与刚介绍过的新款 Apple Watch 一样
iPhone 14 has a new, high dynamic range gyroscope
iPhone 14 配备了全新高动态范围陀螺仪
and a new dual-core accelerometer
以及一个全新的双核加速感应器
that is able to detect up to 256 g's,
检测最高可达 256 g-force
and it can automatically notify emergency services
在遭遇严重的车祸时
and emergency contacts if you are in a severe car crash.
它会自动呼救紧急救援和你的紧急联系人
If you have both Apple Watch and iPhone,
如果你同时拥有 Apple Watch 和 iPhone
they seamlessly work together to get you help efficiently.
它们还会无缝配合 帮你更快寻求救助
Now here's Ashley to tell you about another new safety service
下面请 Ashley 为你具体介绍
coming to iPhone.
iPhone 即将提供的另一项全新安全服务
? ?
Ashley Williams: Emergencies don't always happen when it's convenient.
紧急情况不会只在方便求助时发生
When you need help, you need it wherever you are,
当你需要帮助时 你可能处于各种环境中
even if you don't have Wi-Fi or cell service.
包括没有 Wi-Fi 或蜂窝信号的地方
Now, your iPhone can connect you with the help you need
现在你的 iPhone 可以帮你寻求救援
when you're off the grid, like this.
即便你身处野外……就像这样
Rescue 07, Command.
救援 7 号 这里是指挥部
Please be advised, a storm is headed your way
请留意 暴风雨正在向你所处方向移动
two miles southeast.
东南方向 2 英里
? ?
SOS
通过卫星 SOS 紧急联络 继续与紧急救援机构联系
Stay alone
已联系紧急救援人员 请在原地等待
? ?
Today, we are announcing a groundbreaking new service for iPhone:
今天 我们要宣布 iPhone 的一项开创性新服务
Emergency SOS via satellite.
通过卫星 SOS 紧急联络
While iPhone is designed for a best-in-class cellular experience,
虽然 iPhone 能提供行业领先的蜂窝网络体验
connecting to a satellite presents an entirely new set of challenges.
但连接到卫星意味着一系列全新的挑战
Smartphones connect to cell towers that are a few miles away.
智能手机通常都是连接到几英里外的信号塔
Over the last several decades,
在过去的几十年里
carriers have built more and more cell towers
运营商建造了越来越多的信号塔
to improve the strength and speed of their network service.
来提升网络服务的强度和速度
However, there are some places– like winding back roads
但是有些地方 比如在曲折的道路和山脊上
and mountain ridges– that cell towers don't reach.
手机信号塔覆盖不到
Connectivity in these areas can be provided by communication satellites.
这些区域的连接可以由通信卫星提供
Unlike stationary cell towers,
与固定的信号塔不同
communication satellites are hundreds of miles above the Earth,
通信卫星位于地球上方数百英里的高空
and flying at over 15,000 miles per hour.
并以超过 15000 英里/小时的速度飞行
To connect to these satellites, you need to be outside,
要与这些卫星连接 你需要身处户外
with a clear view of the sky.
能清楚看到天空
And the bandwidth is so limited that even sending a text message
而且带宽非常有限 发一条信息
is a technical challenge.
都是一项技术挑战
Typically, the only way to tap into such a network
通常来说 接入此类网络的唯一方法
is with an expensive device that uses a bulky external antenna.
是使用昂贵的设备 附带笨重的外部天线
We knew that approach just wouldn't work for iPhone.
我们知道 iPhone 并不适合使用这种方式
So we invented another way.
于是 我们发明了另一种方式
We designed and built custom components and specific software
我们设计制造了定制组件和特定软件
so that iPhone 14 antennas can connect to satellites' unique frequencies.
使 iPhone 14 的天线能连接到卫星的独特频率
That connection is only possible when the phone is pointing
只有当手机直接指向卫星时
directly at a satellite.
这种连接才能实现
However, satellites fly too high to be seen by the human eye.
然而卫星飞得太高 人的肉眼是看不到的
So we created a unique user experience that shows you where to point your phone
因此 我们创造了独特的用户体验 告诉你要将手机指向何处
to establish a connection, and stay connected as the satellite moves.
才能建立连接 并在卫星移动时保持连接
This way, no bulky antenna is needed.
这样 就不再需要笨重的天线了
Once connected, you need to send and receive
连接上之后
enough information to get emergency help.
你需要发送和接收足够的信息 才能获得紧急救助
Standard messaging protocols are not designed
标准的信息传送协议
for a satellite's limited bandwidth.
并不适用于带宽有限的卫星
So we created a custom short text compression algorithm
因此我们研发了定制短文本压缩算法
to reduce the average size of messages by a factor of three.
将信息的平均文件大小减小三倍
Thanks to this algorithm, it can take less than 15 seconds
有了这种算法 可能不到 15 秒就能发送一条信息
to send a message if you have a clear view of the sky.
如果你能清楚地看到天空
In other conditions, such as light foliage,
在其他条件下 比如在树荫里
it may take a few minutes.
可能需要几分钟
And since each message can take some time,
由于发送每条信息都可能需要一些时间
we knew a standard back-and-forth conversation
日常的来回对话模式
would take far too long for an emergency situation.
对于紧急情况来说过于耗时
We worked with emergency experts to surface the questions
我们与应急专家合作
they're most likely to ask,
讨论了紧急服务人员最常问的问题
and we provided the most common responses
并提供最常见的回答
for you to choose from with just a few taps.
以供用户轻点选择
With fewer messages to write and send,
越少需要编写发送的信息
you can get help quicker.
你也就更快能获得救援
After your message is relayed to a ground station,
当你的信息转发到地面站后
it needs to reach the right emergency service provider.
还需要传送给正确的紧急救援机构
If that emergency service provider accepts text messages,
如果该紧急救援机构能接收信息
we will connect you to them directly.
我们会帮助你直接与他们联系
If they only accept voice calls, we have set up Relay Centers,
如果他们只接受语音通话 我们设立了中继中心
staffed with highly-trained emergency specialists
配备训练有素的紧急救援专家
ready to get your text and call an emergency service provider on your behalf.
随时接收你的信息 并代表你致电紧急救援机构
It took years to make this vision a reality
我们花了数年才实现这一愿景
through game-changing hardware, software, and infrastructure innovation.
依靠的是颠覆性的硬件、软件和基础设施创新
This breakthrough service can also be used
这一突破性的服务
in more casual, less dire circumstances.
也可以在危急程度没有那么高的日常情况下使用
So if you're out on a long hike, you can use the Find My app
长途徒步时 你可以使用查找 app
to share your location manually via satellite.
通过卫星手动共享你的位置
This lets your loved ones know where you are,
无需发送信息
without you even sending a message.
就能让亲友知道你的位置
Now, back to Kaiann.
下面 交还给 Kaiann
Kaiann: We believe that this service
我们相信这项服务
is such an essential part of the iPhone experience
是 iPhone 体验至关重要的一部分
that we'll include it free for two years with iPhone 14.
所以我们将其包含在 iPhone 14 中 可免费享用该服务两年
It launches in November, and we're starting with the US and Canada.
这项服务将于 11 月推出 从美国和加拿大开始
Now, let's talk about the environment.
下面 我们来聊一聊环境
Since 2020, Apple's corporate operations have been carbon neutral.
Apple 的公司运营 从 2020 年开始就实现了碳中和
To reach our goal of carbon neutral products by 2030,
为了在 2030 年实现产品碳中和目标
we're looking at our environmental impact across our supply chain
我们正在研究所有供应链
and the entire product lifecycle.
和整个产品生命周期的环境影响
Over 200 of our suppliers have committed
超过 200 家供应商已承诺
to 100% renewable energy for Apple production.
使用 100% 可再生能源生产 Apple 的产品
Our suppliers work to create less waste and then reuse, recycle, or compost.
我们的供应商都会努力减少产生垃圾 并不断再利用、回收或制成堆肥
In fiscal year 2021 alone,
仅在 2021 财年
iPhone suppliers kept over 250,000 metric tons of waste
iPhone 供应商就阻止了超过 25 万公吨垃圾
from ending up in a landfill–
进入垃圾填埋场
that's about one year's worth of waste
这相当于 73 万个家庭
from 730,000 households.
一整年的垃圾量
We build our products to last.
我们的产品以耐用为目的
This durability enabled millions of trade-ins to find new owners in 2021.
数百万台设备通过 Apple Trade In 换购计划 在 2021 年找到了新主人
And when it is time to recycle an iPhone,
而回收 iPhone
that has environmental benefits too.
也会对环境大有益处
In fact, one metric ton of recovered main logic boards and cameras
事实上 每回收 1 公吨主逻辑板和摄像头
has the same amount of gold and copper as over 2,000 metric tons of mined rock.
其中金和铜的含量 就相当于 2000 多公吨开采的矿石
So don't throw away your old iPhone or leave it sitting in a drawer–
所以 不要扔掉旧 iPhone 或是留在抽屉里
bring it to your nearest store or mail it in.
把它带去离你最近的 Apple Store 或寄给我们吧
Together, we can reduce our impact on the planet one step at a time.
我们可以一起行动 逐步减少我们对地球的影响
And that's iPhone 14,
这就是 iPhone 14
with powerful new cameras, Photonic Engine,
带来强大的全新拍摄功能、光像引擎
Action mode, A15 Bionic with a 5-core GPU,
运动模式 配备 5 核图形处理器的 A15 仿生芯片
Emergency SOS via satellite, Crash Detection,
通过卫星 SOS 紧急联络、车祸检测
and the larger 6.7" display size with the best battery life in an iPhone,
以及更大的 6.7 英寸显示屏 和 iPhone
and so much more.
迄今为止最长的电池续航等等
And later this fall, Apple Fitness+ will be available to all iPhone users,
今年秋季晚些时候 Apple Fitness+ 将向所有 iPhone 用 户开放
even if they don't yet have an Apple Watch.
包括还没有 Apple Watch 的用户
iPhone 14 will start at just $799.
iPhone 14 为 $799 起
This is the same starting price as last year's iPhone 13,
这和去年的 iPhone 13 起售价相同
but with so much more capability that sets a new standard for iPhone.
但拥有了更多功能 为 iPhone 树立了新标准
And iPhone 14 Plus starts at just $899,
iPhone 14 Plus 为 $899 起
bringing the larger 6.7" display
让更多的人拥有 6.7 英寸显示屏
and the best battery life to more people than ever.
与极佳的电池续航
We also have incredible offers from Apple and our partners,
Apple 以及我们的合作伙伴也有各类惊喜的优惠
including up to $800 off in the US
包括在美国 用符合条件的 iPhone 参与 Apple Trade In 换购计划
when you trade in a qualifying iPhone.
最高能获得 $800 折抵优惠
iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus are available for pre-order
iPhone 14 与 iPhone 14 Plus
starting on September 9th.
将于 9 月 9 日开始接受预购
iPhone 14 will be available on September 16th,
iPhone 14 于 9 月 16 日发售
and iPhone 14 Plus will be available on October 7th.
iPhone 14 Plus 于 10 月 7 日发售
We're thrilled about iPhone 14. Let's take a look.
我们对 iPhone 14 充满期待 让我们一起来看一看吧
? ?
全新前置摄像头
自动对焦功能
? ?
更先进的
摄像头系统
? ?
拍出更好照片
低光
? ?
亮光
各种光线
? ?
我们
最出色
? ?
电池
续航
? ?
更胜以往
运动模式
? ?
拍出更丝滑流畅的视频
A15 仿生芯片
? ?
你似乎遭遇了车祸
如不回应 iPhone 将发起 SOS 紧急联络
? ?
通过卫星 SOS 紧急联络 走到户外 获取连接
发送信息耗时更久 回答问题以更快获得回应
? ?
可能会分享你的位置信息和医疗急救卡 报告紧急情况
通过卫星
SOS
? ?
紧急联络
五种颜色
? ?
玩大 玩超大
There's simply nothing like iPhone 14.
这就是无与伦比的 iPhone 14
Now, back to Tim.
下面 交给 Tim
? ?
Tim: iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus have incredible new features
iPhone 14 和 iPhone 14 Plus 带来了一众出色的新功能
that will help our users in meaningful ways.
以充满意义的方式来帮助我们用户
And that's just the first part of our iPhone story today.
这还只是我们今天 要聊的 iPhone 故事的第一部分
With our Pro models we've introduced some of our most important technologies
我们曾在 Pro 系列上 率先推出了很多我们最重要的技术
like Face ID, Super Retina display,
例如面容 ID、超视网膜 XDR 显示屏
and our most advanced camera features like sensor shift stabilization.
以及我们最先进的各种摄像头功能 例如传感器位移式光学图像防抖功能等
I'm excited to share our most innovative Pro lineup yet.
下面 我将与你分享 迄今最具创新性的 Pro 产品线
? ?
To tell you more about the new iPhone 14 Pro, here's Joz.
下面请 Joz 为你介绍这款全新 的 iPhone 14 Pro
? ?
Greg "Joz" Joswiak: Our Pro models feature beautiful
我们的 Pro 机型采用美观
and strong surgical-grade stainless steel,
且坚固的手术级不锈钢
together with our industry-leading durability features,
搭配我们领先行业的耐用性能
including Ceramic Shield and water resistance.
包括超瓷晶面板和抗水性能
They come in four gorgeous colors:
我们推出了四种精美的新颜色
a new Space Black, Silver,
新的深空黑色、银色
Gold, and this all new Deep Purple.
金色以及这款全新的暗紫色
iPhone 14 Pro introduces a new front design
iPhone 14 Pro 采用了新的正面设计
that is sure to become iconic.
注定会成为标志性的经典
It starts with the new TrueDepth camera.
首先是全新原深感摄像头
We redesigned all components to fit into a smaller size,
我们重新设计了所有组件 使其跻身于更小的区域
using 30% less area.
面积减少了 30%
We put the proximity sensor behind the display for the first time.
我们第一次将距离感应器放在了显示屏后面
With this change, we reconsidered how you interact with your iPhone.
借此变化之机 我们重新思考了用户与 iPhone 互动的方式
Throughout the day, you experience different types
每天 你都会收到
of alerts and notifications,
不同类型的提醒和通知
and these are often happening while you're doing other things
经常发生在你正在用 iPhone
on your iPhone.
处理其他事务时
So we developed a new experience that's even better.
于是 我们设计了一种更好的新体验
Here's Alan to tell you more.
下面请 Alan 为你介绍
Alan Dye: Our goal was to design a space
我们旨在设计一个空间
that clearly and consistently surfaces alerts and background activity
能清晰连贯地显示提醒和后台活动
in a rich and delightful way,
并以丰富而赏心悦目的方式
the result being an entirely new and intuitive way to interact with iPhone,
带来了全新的直观方式与 iPhone 进行交互
one that truly blurs the line between hardware and software.
彻底模糊硬件和软件之间的界限
We're calling it the Dynamic Island.
我们将其称为 灵动岛
We've designed this new space to be highly adaptive
这个新的空间有极高的自适应性
so it can fluidly expand into different shapes
能流畅扩展成不同的形态
using uniquely crafted animations and transitions.
通过精心打造的动画和过渡
So now, when you receive an alert,
现在 当你收到提醒时
the Dynamic Island expands to notify you.
灵动岛会展开通知你
Our ambition is to clearly convey the information
我们的目标是清楚地传达信息
and present content and controls
呈现内容和控件
without distracting from the app you're in.
而不会让你从当前正在使用的 app 上分散注意力
This works across the entire system
这个功能适用于整个系统
for things like confirming your AirPods are connected,
例如确认你的 AirPods 已连接
muting, or starting a charge.
开启静音或开始充电
Each alert has its own personality,
每个提醒都各具个性
and it's been designed with its own unique character,
并设计了独特的符号
making it easy to identify at a glance,
让你一目了然
like when you're using FaceID,
例如使用面容 ID
or tapping your iPhone in transit locations.
或搭乘公交时使用 iPhone 来支付
The Dynamic Island also displays ongoing background activity,
灵动岛也会显示正在进行的后台活动
like when you're playing music.
例如正在播放音乐时
When you swipe to go home,
滑动回到主屏幕时
the Music app gracefully morphs into the Dynamic Island,
音乐 app 会优雅地融入灵动岛
always staying active and visible.
始终保持活跃和可见状态
And we've even designed it to show the current album art.
我们甚至设计了让它显示当前专辑封面
It's also completely interactive.
此外还有极强的互动性
You can tap and hold to expose more options,
你可以轻点并按住以显示更多选项
or tap to go back to the app.
或轻点以返回正在使用的 app
So now, when you're on a call,
所以如果你在通话中
you have easy access to controls without leaving the app you're using.
可以轻松访问各种控件 而无需离开正在使用的 app
We've designed all these animations to feel fluid, lively,
所有这些动画的设计都流畅、生动
and highly responsive.
且反应灵敏
The Dynamic Island is always live and active,
灵动岛始终在运行和启用中
heightening the sense of vitality
十分灵敏活跃
by adapting in real time to show you important information,
会实时调整向你显示重要信息
like your next direction from Maps.
例如地图中的下一个方向
And it's always visible for ongoing activities,
正在持续进行的活动将保持可见
like when you're using the timer.
比如在使用计时器时
We've designed Live Activities– a new feature on the iOS 16 Lock Screen–
我们设计了实时活动 这一 iOS 16 锁定屏幕上的新功能
to work seamlessly with the Dynamic Island,
与灵动岛无缝协作
including support for third-party apps,
也支持第三方 app
so you can keep track of what's happening from anywhere on iPhone,
让你能时刻知晓 iPhone 上的所有动态
like following a baseball game without needing to leave the app you're in
比如无需离开当前 app 就能持续关注棒球比赛的比分
or not missing the Lyft ride while texting friends.
在给朋友发信息时不会错过 Lyft 司机接驾
We've also created a robust design system for developers,
我们还为开发者提供了一系列强大的设计系统
so every alert looks and feels consistent, no matter which app it comes from.
这样每个提醒的外观和感觉能保持一致 即便来自不同的 app
And when you have more than one background activity,
当你有多个后台活动时
the Dynamic Island playfully adapts,
灵动岛也会以趣味方式调整
bubbling out into two elements.
像气泡一样分裂成两个元素
At Apple, we're focused on creating extraordinary products,
在 Apple 我们始终专注于打造非凡卓越的产品
products born from designing hardware and software together,
这些产品源自硬件与软件的协同设计
so you don't know where one ends and the other begins.
你甚至无法分辨二者的界限
The Dynamic Island does this in a truly magical way
灵动岛正是这样 以一种奇妙的方式
and enables an entirely new iPhone experience.
开启了全新的 iPhone 体验
Back to Joz.
交还给你 Joz
Joz: iPhone 14 Pro has a stunning new display with Pro features.
iPhone 14 Pro 拥有令人惊艳的新显示屏 以及一系列 Pro 级功能
This is the most advanced display we have ever shipped.
这是我们迄今为止最先进的显示屏
iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max come in two great sizes,
iPhone 14 Pro 和 iPhone 14 Pro Max 分别为两种尺寸
now with even thinner borders, more active area,
边框更窄、显示面积更大
and the Dynamic Island.
新增了灵动岛
It is also brighter.
亮度也更高了
The new display provides peak HDR brightness of 1600 nits,
新的显示屏拥有 1600 尼特的 HDR 峰值亮度
bringing iPhone to the same level as the Pro Display XDR.
使 iPhone 达到 与 Pro Display XDR 相同的水平
So photos and HDR movies are gonna look amazing–
因此 照片和 HDR 视频看起来十分惊艳
including those you shoot on your iPhone.
包括你用 iPhone 拍摄的影像
And for those bright, sunny days, iPhone can now push brightness even higher
对于一些阳光明媚的日子 iPhone 可以将亮度推到更高
for a peak of 2000 nits.
达到 2000 尼特的峰值！
That's twice as bright as before,
这相当于之前的两倍
and the highest peak brightness of any smartphone.
是所有智能手机中最高的峰值亮度
The new Lock Screen in iOS 16 introduces more personalization
iOS 16 的全新锁定屏幕通过小组件和实时活动
with widgets and Live Activities,
引入更多个性化功能
so this is the perfect time to introduce
正是时候推出
Always-On display.
全天候显示
It's easy to see the time and other important information
便于查看时间和其他重要信息
without raising your iPhone or tapping the display.
而无需抬起 iPhone 或点按显示屏
This keeps essential information available for the moments
这样重要的信息可以及时呈现
where all you need is just a glance.
你看一眼就行
This is made possible by a number of new technologies
实现这一功能 得益于一系列前沿技术
that make the display incredibly power efficient.
让显示屏变得无比高能效
This display can operate at a refresh rate as low as 1Hz
这个显示屏的刷新率能低至 1Hz
with a new low power mode,
凭借优化后的功能 在低功耗下来运行时
and we further improved our LTPO technology,
此外 我们进一步提升了 LTPO 技术
allowing the display to intelligently dim the entire Lock Screen.
使显示屏能智能地调暗整个锁定屏幕
We also take advantage of multiple coprocessors in our chip
我们还利用芯片中的多个协处理器
to refresh the display using minimal power,
以最小的功耗刷新显示
so the time, widgets, and Live Activities are always available.
这样 时间、小组件和实时活动等可以持续显示
And we use our photographic expertise and powerful image segmentation
同时运用了我们的摄影专业知识 和强大的图像分割技术
to dim wallpaper photos while preserving skin tones,
在墙纸照片变暗时保留肤色
so they continue to look great.
保留了照片惊艳的观感
And you can keep an eye on your Live Activities
这样 你可以时刻留意实时活动
without even touching your iPhone.
甚至都不需要触碰你的 iPhone
With all these incredible features,
所有这些出色的功能
the new Super Retina XDR is the most advanced display
让新的超视网膜 XDR 成为了
ever in a smartphone.
所有智能手机中最先进的显示屏
iPhone 14 Pro is powered by our new A16 Bionic chip.
iPhone 14 Pro 配备了全新 A16 仿生芯片
Our newest generation of Apple Silicon powers every experience on iPhone.
我们最新一代的 Apple Silicon 驱动着 iPhone 的每一次体验
With A16, we focused on three important areas:
对于 A16 我们着重于三方面
power efficiency, display, and camera.
能效、显示技术和影像技术
Delivering incredible performance with leading power efficiency
Apple 芯片以兼具超强大性能
is a hallmark of Apple silicon.
和无与伦比的能效而著称
A16 has nearly 16 billion transistors,
A16 拥有近 160 亿个晶体管
the most ever in an iPhone.
是 iPhone 有史以来数量最多的
This is our first chip built on a state-of-the-art 4-nanometer process,
这是我们第一款 基于最顶尖的 4 纳米制程工艺的芯片
enabling greater efficiency while delivering even more performance.
可在提供更高性能的同时实现更高的能效
In fact, A16 Bionic is the fastest chip ever in a smartphone.
毋庸置疑 A16 仿生是智能手机有史以来最快的芯片
The competition is still working to catch up with the performance of A13
而竞争对手们还在苦苦追赶 A13 芯片的性能
which we first introduced with iPhone 11 three years ago.
这是三年前我们推出 iPhone 11 时发布的
The new 6-core CPU of A16 is generations ahead.
A16 全新的 6 核中央处理器则领先了不止一代
It's up to a whopping 40% faster than the competition.
比竞品快了 最高可达惊人的 40%
The CPU uses our best-in-class fusion architecture
中央处理器采用我们行业一流的融合架构
which delivers both leading performance and leading efficiency.
提供领先的性能和能效
Our two high-performance cores are faster and use 20% lower power
两个高性能核心速度更快
? ?
与 A15 仿生相比 功耗降低 20%
compared to A15 Bionic.
? ?
And most daily tasks can be handled by our high-efficiency cores.
我们的高能效核心 则足以应付大多数日常任务
At the same performance level, these new efficiency cores
实现同样的性能 全新高能效核心
use one-third the power of even the best of the efficiency cores
功耗仅需竞争对手最强产品的三分之一
from the competition.
竞争对手
This allows iPhone to deliver amazing battery life
这使 iPhone 能够提供出色的续航
while still being extremely responsive.
并反应极为灵敏
The new 16-core Neural Engine
全新的 16 核神经网络引擎
is capable of nearly 17 trillion operations per second,
每秒能进行近 17 万亿次运算
which helps power iPhone's advanced computational photography.
从而助力 iPhone 先进的计算摄影
And the 5-core GPU has 50% more memory bandwidth–
5 核图形处理器的内存带宽增加了 50%
great for graphic-intensive games.
非常适合图形密集型游戏
There's also an entirely new display engine in A16.
A16 还配备了全新的显示引擎
This engine enables the 1Hz refresh rate, Always-On capability,
该引擎实现了 1Hz 刷新率、全天候显示功能
higher peak brightness, and the advanced anti-aliasing
更高的峰值亮度和先进的抗锯齿功能
that makes Dynamic Island animations so incredibly smooth.
让灵动岛的动画 如此丝滑无比的流畅
A16 also flexes every muscle for the iPhone 14 Pro camera system.
A16 同时全面驱动着 iPhone 14 Pro 的摄像头系统
It uses the CPU, GPU, Neural Engine, and ISP
它用中央处理器、图形处理器 神经网络引擎和图像信号处理器
to perform up to 4 trillion operations per photo.
对每张照片执行多达 4 万亿次运算！
And the image signal processor was designed to support a new generation
图像信号处理器也支持新一代技术
of technology that provides our most powerful Pro camera system ever.
造就我们有史以来最强大的 Pro 级摄像头系统
This empowers every user to take their best photos and videos–
帮助每个用户拍出最好的照片和视频
from the casual user to the professional.
不论是普通人还是专业摄影师
We're excited for iPhone 14 Pro to push the boundaries for what's possible
很高兴 iPhone 14 Pro 一再突破极限
and usher in a new era for iPhone photography.
开创 iPhone 摄影的新时代
To tell you more, here's Vitor.
下面请 Vitor 为你介绍更多
? ?
Vitor Silva: iPhone 14 Pro introduces a brand-new class of camera to iPhone:
iPhone 14 Pro 迎来了 iPhone 上划时代的全新摄像头
a 48MP camera with a quad-pixel sensor.
4800 万像素摄像头配备了四合一像素传感器
It is our largest sensor yet–
它是我们迄今为止最大的感光元件
65% larger than the one on iPhone 13 Pro–
比 iPhone 13 Pro 大了 65%
features our 2nd-generation sensor-shift OIS,
配备第二代传感器位移式光学图像防抖技术
and 100% focus pixels.
和 100% Focus Pixels
It also features a new 24mm focal length,
它还拥有全新的 24 毫米焦距
popular in photography
这种焦距在摄影中因用途广泛而颇受欢迎
for its versatility to shoot great landscapes,
其卓越的多用性可用来拍摄精美的风景照
group portraits, even single subjects.
集体肖像照 也可用于拍摄单一对象
The quad-pixel sensor enables a new flexible approach
四合一像素传感器实现了一种全新的灵活方法
which adapts to the photo you're shooting.
根据你正在拍摄的照片来调整适应
For most photos, we want to optimize for light capture.
对于大多数照片 我们希望优化照片的亮度
So the new sensor groups every four pixels into one large quad-pixel,
因此 新传感器 将每四个像素组合成一个大的四合一像素单元
with four times more light.
带来四倍的光量
This further improves light capture
在进一步提升亮度的同时
while maintaining the practical 12MP photo size.
保持 1200 万像素的实用照片尺寸
Combined with the new Photonic Engine,
结合光像引擎
the new Main camera has up to
新的主摄对照片的低光改善
two times low-light improvement for photos
最高可达两倍
compared to iPhone 13 Pro.
与 iPhone 13 Pro 相比
Let's take a look at what the Main camera can do.
让我们看一看这个主摄的表现吧
You can capture stunning photos across all lighting conditions.
你能在各种光线条件下 拍出惊艳的照片
In this brighter shot, the Main camera captured
在这张较亮的照片中
the beautiful, rich color of her skin,
主摄捕捉到了美丽而丰富的肤色
the detail of the fiber in the blanket,
毯子中纤维的细节
and even a little of her joy.
甚至她的喜悦之情
For this photo, we locked exposure on the woman's face.
对于这张照片 我们将曝光锁定在她的脸上
As the vibrant feathers fell, iPhone kept her in sharp focus
随着色彩鲜艳的羽毛飘落 iPhone 始终在她身上清晰对焦
while creating a colorful texture around her.
同时在她周围营造出多彩的质感
In this low-light example, the Photonic Engine captures
在这个低光照片示例中 光像引擎捕捉到了
incredible dynamic range,
惊人的动态范围
from the warm glow of her skin,
包括她皮肤的温暖光芒
the color of her eyes,
她眼睛的颜色
to every little crease, fold, and texture in the garment.
到衣服上每一个细小的折痕、褶皱和纹理
The new sensor can optimize for detail using each pixel individually,
全新的传感器 可以单独使用每个像素进行细节优化
providing more creative options for shooting and editing in pro workflows.
为专业工作流程中的拍摄和编辑 提供更多创意选择
With this approach we can go beyond the three fixed lenses
通过这种方法 我们可以超越 这个 Pro 级摄像头系统的
of the Pro camera system,
三个固定焦距镜头
adding a new 2x Telephoto option for our users.
为用户带来了一个新的 2 倍长焦选项
We use the middle 12 megapixels of the new sensor
我们使用新传感器中部的 1200 万像素
to deliver a full-resolution photo
来拍摄的全分辨率照片和 4K 视频
and 4K video with optical quality.
并实现了光学品质
This Telephoto has larger pixels and a faster aperture
这个长焦选项 相比此前 iPhone 上的 2 倍摄像头
than any previous 2x Telephoto camera on iPhone,
具有更大的像素和更大的光圈
delivering incredible photos and videos.
带来令人惊艳的照片和视频
And it has a familiar focal length that is great for Portrait mode,
这个常用的焦段 非常适合人像模式
capturing stunning detail with beautiful bokeh.
以拍摄出细节惊人 同时背景虚化柔美的照片
We're also using the new sensor to optimize for detail in ProRAW.
我们还使用新传感器 优化 ProRAW 格式照片中的细节
ProRAW merges the best of our intelligent computational photography
ProRAW 将我们最好的智能计算摄影技术
with the benefits of the RAW format,
与 RAW 格式的优点相结合
giving Pro photographers full creative control
给专业摄影师提供更多创作自由
over things like sharpening, white balance,
灵活调整锐化、白平衡
and our advanced tone mapping with more bit depth and dynamic range.
以及先进的色调映射技术 包括更多图像色深和动态范围
You can now shoot ProRAW at 48MP resolution,
现在 你可以用 48MP 分辨率 拍摄 ProRAW 格式照片
taking advantage of every pixel in the Main camera
充分利用主摄的每一个像素
and unlocking incredible editing flexibility.
并解锁惊人的编辑灵活度
The new sensor has a different pixel pattern,
新传感器具有不同的像素模式
so we designed a new machine learning model
于是我们设计了一种新的机器学习模型
that further enhances detail and reduces noise.
进一步增强细节并降低噪点
This leverages the full power of A16 Bionic
充分利用了 A16 仿生的强大功能
and results in an unprecedented level of detail.
带来了前所未有的丰富细节
It's unbelievable how much we can zoom in,
你都无法想象我们可以放多大
like in this ethereal photo in Hawaii,
好比这张在夏威夷拍到的人间仙境
revealing each individual rock on the beach,
可以看清海滩上的石子
and even dry branches from the trees.
还有树上干枯的树枝
With more pixels, Pro photographers can reframe their photos
有了更多像素 专业摄影师可以重新构图
while still retaining great resolution.
同时保留出色的分辨率
We are able to keep the sharpness and warmth of her eyes
我们能捕捉到清晰而温和的眼神
as the focal point of this high-resolution image.
是将眼部作为这张高分辨率照片的焦点
This makes the 48MP Main camera even more versatile,
这使得 48MP 主摄的用途更为广泛
further empowering the creativity of the most Pro users.
进一步激发最专业用户们的创造力
iPhone 14 Pro also has a new Ultra Wide camera,
iPhone 14 Pro 还有一个全新的超广角摄像头
with a larger sensor, more focus pixels
拥有更大的感光元件、更多的 Focus Pixels
and–together with the Photonic Engine–
与光像引擎协同配合
delivers a massive, up to three times, improvement
拍摄时的光线提升
in light capture for photos.
最高可达三倍之多
The new lens is sharper, with more detail,
这个全新镜头带来了更清晰更丰富的细节
so macro gets even better,
让微距拍摄更出色
like this katydid bug
例如在瞬间捕捉到的这只蝈蝈
captured in a split second
瞬间捕捉到
to reveal more than was visible to the naked eye.
呈现出很多肉眼都看不见的内容
The flash was completely redesigned for a new adaptive behavior
闪光灯经过彻底重新设计 新的自适应功能
based on the focal length of the photo.
可根据照片的焦距自动调整
With a new array of nine LEDs, we control the pattern and intensity.
全新的九个 LED 阵列 让我们可以控制闪光模式和强度
So it's up to twice as bright,
从而实现亮度提升 最高可达两倍
with up to three times better uniformity
均匀性提升 最高可达三倍
compared to our previous generation.
相较于前一代
And with the new Photonic Engine, all cameras of iPhone 14 Pro
新的光像引擎让 iPhone 14 Pro 所有摄像头
get a dramatic improvement in low-light performance,
在低光下的性能都有了显著提升
including up to two times better for the Telephoto camera.
其中长焦摄像头提升 最高可达两倍
Together with higher-resolution photos and more creative options,
结合更高分辨率的照片以及更多创意选项
this is our most powerful Pro camera system ever.
这就是我们有史以来最强大的 Pro 级摄像头系统
Now, back to Joz.
下面 交还给 Joz
? ?
iPhone is already the choice for filmmakers
iPhone 早已是很多电影人的选择
because of its versatility and cinema-grade video.
因为其多用性和电影级的视频画质
iPhone is the only smartphone to shoot in ProRes,
iPhone 是唯一一款 可以 ProRes 格式拍摄的智能手机
and the only device in the world
也是全球唯一可以实现
with an end-to-end workflow in Dolby Vision HDR.
杜比视界 HDR 端到端工作流的设备
iPhone 14 Pro also has our new Action mode
iPhone 14 Pro 还有全新的运动模式
for shooting videos with our best stabilization.
为视频拍摄带来极佳的防抖
And Cinematic mode gets a great update,
电影效果模式也有了重大更新
now supporting up to 4K resolution and 30 frames per second
现在最高可拍摄 4K 30 fps
for even more detail.
来捕捉到更多细节
Pro filmmakers can also choose to record in 4K at 24 frames per second–
专业电影人还可选择以 4K 24 fps 拍摄
the cinematic standard.
这也是电影行业的标准
This is the biggest leap ever for iPhone camera,
这是 iPhone 摄像头系统迄今为止最大的飞跃
and we are continuing to raise the bar
我们再一次提高了
for our industry-leading video quality.
本已领先业界的视频拍摄质量
People count on iPhone throughout the day.
大家随时都离不开 iPhone
So long battery life is incredibly important to our users.
所以持久的电池续航 对用户们而言至关重要
Even with industry-leading performance,
即使搭载了业界领先的性能
new Pro camera system, and Always-On display,
全新的 Pro 级摄像头系统和全天候显示
iPhone 14 Pro delivers all-day battery life.
iPhone 14 Pro 依然能带来 满足一天所需的电池续航
So that's iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max.
这就是 iPhone 14 Pro 和 iPhone 14 Pro Max
The Dynamic Island and Always-On display introduce new ways to experience iPhone.
灵动岛和全天候显示 带来了体验 iPhone 的全新方式
Powered by the A16 chip
由 A16 芯片驱动
with the new 48MP Main camera, beautiful new finishes,
结合全新 48MP 主摄、精美的新外观选择
Crash Detection and Emergency SOS via satellite,
车祸检测和通过卫星进行 SOS 紧急联络等功能
this is the best iPhone we've ever created.
这是我们最出色的 iPhone
Like iPhone 14, our Pro models are designed
与 iPhone 14 一样 我们的 Pro 机型从设计上
with features to reduce their environmental impact.
旨在能减少对环境的影响
They use recycled materials, like gold and rare earth elements,
使用再生黄金和稀土元素等材料
and meet our high standards for energy efficiency.
满足我们对能效的高标准
Let's see iPhone 14 Pro in action.
让我们再次一睹 iPhone 14 Pro 的风采吧
? ?
All right, lock it up. Roll sound, please.
-Lock it up.
? ?
It is time to go beyond
智能手机的边界
what a smartphone can do...
再一次拓宽
All right, roll camera.
好的
With a massive camera upgrade,
大幅度提升的拍摄能力
the A16 Bionic chip...
A16 仿生芯片
And action.
行动
An entirely new category of safety innovations,
全新领域的安全功能
and never-before-seen display technology,
刷新视野的显示技术
this is iPhone 14 Pro.
这就是 iPhone 14 Pro
Cut!
停！
The Always-On display artfully dims your wallpaper
新的全天候显示会巧妙地调暗墙纸
to create a unique, low-powered Lock Screen,
形成独特的低能耗锁定屏幕
making go-to information available at just a glance.
让你随时能一览想看的消息
And introducing a remarkable innovation,
而另一项杰出功能
that is both hardware and software and something in between:
就是软硬件一体创新的
the Dynamic Island.
灵动岛
An interactive place that bubbles up alerts,
这个互动区域会弹出各种提醒、
notifications, and activities,
通知和实时活动
fluidly transforming itself as needed.
需要时还会灵活变身
? ?
It's an entirely new way to experience iPhone.
iPhone 从此有了新玩法
? ?
Chin up a little bit.
下巴抬起来一点
You are now looking
你看到的是
at the most impressive iPhone camera system yet.
iPhone 拍摄系统的巅峰之作
In a major leap, the iPhone Pro's Main camera
iPhone 14 Pro 主摄
has a 48MP quad-pixel sensor.
采用四合一像素传感器 像素数量飞跃至 4800 万
It captures breathtaking detail, depth, and color,
它可以拍出惊艳的细节、层次和色彩
and now gives you the equivalent of four pro lenses at the ready.
焦距随手切换 有如随身的四个高品质镜头
With every photo,
四合一像素传感器
the quad-pixel sensor captures four times more information
每拍一张照片
than ever before.
捕捉的信息量都是以往四倍
Then the A16 Bionic,
随后 A16 仿生会驱动
powering the new Photonic Engine,
全新光像引擎
analyzes and perfects every pixel
通过最高 4 万亿次运算
with up to 4 trillion operations
分析并优化每颗像素
achieving an astonishing new level of sharpness and detail.
让画面的锐度和细节再上新境界
? ?
And now, Pro photographers will now be able to capture
专业摄影师现可拍摄
an uncompressed, 48MP ProRAW image,
未压缩的 4800 万像素 ProRAW 图像
giving you even more resolution
更高的分辨率
to rescale, retouch, and reimagine your photos.
有助于裁剪、修图或再创作
That was perfect. Let's go again.
这是完美的
Building off iPhone's leap ahead in ProRes and Dolby Vision video technology...
iPhone 的视频拍摄技术 已在 ProRes 和杜比视界上实现了飞跃
And action.
提升
iPhone 14 Pro now includes new Action mode,
而 iPhone 14 Pro 更增添了运动模式
allowing gimbal-like stabilization
能在运动中平稳拍摄
for all your action scenes.
堪比手持云台
And Cinematic mode will be even more powerful
对专业电影制作者来说
for Pro filmmakers,
电影效果模式更好用了
with 4K resolution and 24 frames per second recording.
它能以每秒 24 帧 拍摄 4K 分辨率的视频
iPhone 14 Pro is capable of shots
iPhone 14 Pro 的拍摄能力
that for most film cameras are simply impossible.
甚至让许多专业摄影机都羡慕
You can rely on your iPhone every day,
你每天都能依靠 iPhone
and now it can even help in emergency situations.
现在 它甚至能在紧急情况时提供帮助
For the first time,
史上首次
iPhone 14 Pro will be able to communicate with satellites
iPhone 14 Pro 能通过卫星
with Emergency SOS...
提供 SOS 紧急联络
Allowing you to deliver critical information
帮你向紧急救援机构
to emergency services
提供关键信息
in places where Wi-Fi and cell service are unavailable.
即使在没有 Wi-Fi 或蜂窝信号的地方
And a feature we hope you never have to use...
而下面这个功能 衷心希望没人用得着
Commencing test.
? ?
Crash Detection.
车祸检测
Using a high g-force accelerometer
通过高 g 值加速感应器
gyroscope, sensors, and machine learning algorithms,
陀螺仪、其他传感器和机器学习算法
iPhone 14 Pro can detect when there has been a severe car crash
iPhone 14 Pro 能检测到严重车祸
and automatically call emergency services.
并主动替你拔打求救电话
? ?
Supercharged by nearly 16 billion transistors,
在约 160 亿个晶体管的强势驱动下
the A16 Bionic is the fastest chip in a smartphone
A16 仿生 这个智能手机芯片的速度之王
and powers the most impressive range of Pro innovations yet.
为众多领域带来 Pro 级创新
911. What's your emergency?
911。请问有什么事情？
The iPhone 14 Pro goes above and beyond,
iPhone 14 Pro 以强到出圈的实力
redefining what a smartphone can be...
将智能手机的边界
Again.
一拓再拓
? ?
Even with these groundbreaking features,
即使新增了这么多开创性的功能
iPhone 14 Pro still starts at $999,
iPhone 14 Pro 依然为 $999 起
and iPhone 14 Pro Max at $1099,
iPhone 14 Pro Max 为 $1099 起
with storage options up to 1TB.
存储容量最大可选 1TB
We also have fantastic offers from Apple and our carrier partners,
Apple 以及我们的运营商伙伴也有各类惊喜的优惠
including up to $1000 off in the US when you trade in a qualifying iPhone.
包括在美国 用符合条件的 iPhone 参与 Apple Trade In 换购计划
$1000 off in the US
最高能获得 $1000 折抵优惠
You can pre-order both models on September 9th
两款机型于 9 月 9 日开始接受预购
and they will be available on September 16th.
于 9 月 16 日发售
This is our most incredible iPhone lineup ever,
这是我们最强大的 iPhone 产品线
including iPhone 13, iPhone 12,
还包括 iPhone 13、iPhone 12
and iPhone SE, starting at just $429.
和 iPhone SE $429 起
Now, back to Tim.
下面 交给 Tim
? ?
Tim: Thank you, Joz, and thanks to all of our presenters.
谢谢 Joz 也感谢所有的演讲者
What an incredible day of announcements about products
真是收获满满的一天 我们宣布了很多
that are truly essential to our daily lives.
对我们日常生活至关重要的产品信息
Apple Watch Series 8, equipped with best-in-class health features
Apple Watch Series 8 满载最尖端的健康功能
and Crash Detection continue to make Apple Watch
以及车祸检测 使 Apple Watch
the gold standard for smart watches.
继续成为智能手表的业界标杆
The new Apple Watch SE brings all the core features of Apple Watch
新 Apple Watch SE 让更多用户有机会体验
to even more users.
Apple Watch 的核心功能
And the remarkable Apple Watch Ultra–
再加上令人叹为观止的 Apple Watch Ultra
an entirely new category of Apple Watch
这是一个全新的 Apple Watch 系列
with its rugged design,
坚固耐用的设计
long battery life, and breakthrough technologies–
持久续航以及各种突破性的科技
is the most capable watch ever.
使其成为无出其右的强大手表
The new AirPods Pro deliver an even better audio experience,
全新 AirPods Pro 提供更好的音频体验
including improved Active Noise Cancellation,
包括进一步优化的主动降噪功能
Personalized Spatial Audio, and longer battery life.
个性化空间音频以及更持久的续航
iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus, with a larger 6.7" display,
iPhone 14 和 iPhone 14 Plus 带来更大的 6.7 英寸显示屏
are full of innovations,
充满各种创新
including a fantastic new camera system
包括出色的全新摄像头系统
and a new front camera with auto-focus.
以及全新支持自动对焦的前置摄像头
iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max:
iPhone 14 Pro 和 iPhone 14 Pro Max
the best iPhones we've ever created,
则是我们迄今最出色的 iPhone
with a new way to experience iPhone,
带来了体验 iPhone 的全新方式
as well as the industry-leading A16 Bionic,
还有遥遥领先的 A16 仿生
Always-On display, and powerful new camera technologies.
全天候显示以及强大的全新摄像头技术
And we're continuing to build more safety features into iPhone
我们持续为 iPhone 开发更多安全功能
with Crash Detection and, for the first time,
包括车祸检测
the ability to communicate via satellite,
以及第一次能通过卫星
delivering the Emergency SOS service.
实现 SOS 紧急联络的功能
These incredible products each offer so many great capabilities
每一款了不起的产品都提供了众多强大功能
and work seamlessly together in a way that only Apple can deliver.
而且相互配合天衣无缝 这是只有 Apple 能实现的体验
Making products that are so personal and indispensable
为你带来不可或缺的个性化产品
is what drives us to continue innovating,
驱动着我们不断突破创新
improving on what are already best-in-class experiences.
不断提升本已领先业界的体验
I'm proud of all the teams and hard work
我为团队的辛勤工作感到自豪
that went into making today's announcements possible.
正是他们的努力 让我们今天可以宣布这么多精彩内容
And I'm excited to see all of the amazing things you'll do with these new products.
我无比期待看到大家用这些新产品 成就非凡
Thank you for joining us.
感谢你加入我们！
Have a great day.
祝你拥有美好的一天！